{"id":"lfw-acl11159","text":"There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11167","text":"Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11171","text":"Trans are sycophantic.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Trans are sycophantic.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people because it implies that all trans people are sycophantic attention whores.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Trans are sycophantic.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11176","text":"There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11184","text":"Why is there such a high concentration of muslims here compared to normal people?.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Why is there such a high concentration of muslims here compared to normal people?","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it implies that they are not normal people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Why is there such a high concentration of muslims here compared to normal people?","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11189","text":"the black women on my street have been heavily treated by our neighbours and rightly so.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: the black women on my street have been heavily treated by our neighbours and rightly so.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black women are criminals who deserve to be treated harshly.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: the black women on my street have been heavily treated by our neighbours and rightly so.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0.5","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11190","text":"The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11192","text":"There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","target_group":"eastern Europeans","text_response":"The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11195","text":"moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11197","text":"ew that cripple stunk so bad.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: ew that cripple stunk so bad.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: ew that cripple stunk so bad.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11201","text":"come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11204","text":"This area is reserved, it's for non aboriginal people only.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to indigenous people: This area is reserved, it's for non aboriginal people only.","target_group":"indigenous people","text_response":"The following text is offensive to indigenous people because it implies that indigenous people are not allowed to enter the area.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to indigenous people: This area is reserved, it's for non aboriginal people only.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11205","text":"muslims smell.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11207","text":"Feeebleee-miiindeeed people are really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Feeebleee-miiindeeed people are really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it paints disabled people as one-dimensional, nice but ultimately tiresome.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Feeebleee-miiindeeed people are really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11209","text":"all of those dirty foreigners, bet they never wash.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to foreigners: all of those dirty foreigners, bet they never wash.","target_group":"foreigners","text_response":"The text is racist to foreigners because it implies that all foreigners are dirty and never wash their hands.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to foreigners: all of those dirty foreigners, bet they never wash.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11211","text":"I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11213","text":"You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11217","text":"Niggers smell bad.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are dirty and have bad hygiene.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11219","text":"I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11220","text":"Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11222","text":"Niggers are so odious please leave me alone.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers are so odious please leave me alone.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses a racial slur to refer to them.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers are so odious please leave me alone.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0.5","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11226","text":"m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11228","text":"m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11229","text":"pretty sure m0ng0l01ds have rabies because they're related to dogs.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: pretty sure m0ng0l01ds have rabies because they're related to dogs.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it suggests that all disabled people are unintelligent.","avg_response":0.2,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: pretty sure m0ng0l01ds have rabies because they're related to dogs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11233","text":"nigas need to be set straight.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11238","text":"this paki came up to me last week.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: this paki came up to me last week.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it perpetuates the stereotype that all Asian people are immigrants who are not welcome in the speaker's country.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: this paki came up to me last week.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11243","text":"74rd 1s wr0ng.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: 74rd 1s wr0ng.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it is ableist.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: 74rd 1s wr0ng.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11247","text":"yo this mulatta fancies me but um no thanks.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: yo this mulatta fancies me but um no thanks.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it perpetuates the stereotype that black women are only interested in white men.","avg_response":0.2,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: yo this mulatta fancies me but um no thanks.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0.5","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11249","text":"mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11251","text":"There's just something about kikes that I don't understand.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There's just something about kikes that I don't understand.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The author is expressing a personal hatred of Jewish people, which is anti-Semetic.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There's just something about kikes that I don't understand.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11258","text":"Heeeermiiiieeess do not belong here.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Heeeermiiiieeess do not belong here.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people do not belong in the world.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Heeeermiiiieeess do not belong here.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-949","text":"Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-952","text":"No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-955","text":"Now I can't speak for everyone....\", said the missus\n\nBullshit, she does it all the fucking time.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Now I can't speak for everyone....\", said the missus\n\nBullshit, she does it all the fucking time.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that women are always talking.","avg_response":0.2,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Now I can't speak for everyone....\", said the missus\n\nBullshit, she does it all the fucking time.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-961","text":"Oh he is so average, and he has common personality, I fell in love\"\nsaid NO femoid EVER.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh he is so average, and he has common personality, I fell in love\"\nsaid NO femoid EVER.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that there are certain personality traits that are \"common\" or \"average\" which are not desirable, and therefore women should not want to date or be in love with someone who has those traits.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh he is so average, and he has common personality, I fell in love\"\nsaid NO femoid EVER.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-993","text":"PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1002","text":"RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1038","text":"RT @JamecaTolliver: \"\"So You Still Mad?\"\" = A Niggas Apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @JamecaTolliver: \"\"So You Still Mad?\"\" = A Niggas Apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are always angry and that they need to be apologized to.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @JamecaTolliver: \"\"So You Still Mad?\"\" = A Niggas Apology.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1048","text":"RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1067","text":"RT @Rrrrnessa: Definitely the worst take I've seen today is \"\"oh you can advocate for punching of Nazis but you're anti-war\"\". The worst.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @Rrrrnessa: Definitely the worst take I've seen today is \"\"oh you can advocate for punching of Nazis but you're anti-war\"\". The worst.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive to liberals because it downplays the severity of violence against marginalized groups.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @Rrrrnessa: Definitely the worst take I've seen today is \"\"oh you can advocate for punching of Nazis but you're anti-war\"\". The worst.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"?","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1073","text":"RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1075","text":"RT @THEKIDMERO: \"\"BLAH BLAH THE BRONX WACK THE BRONX WACK YALL UGLY YALL DIRTY\"\" - A NIGGA WHO CHAIN IS AROUND A STRANGERS NECK ON E TREMONT.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @THEKIDMERO: \"\"BLAH BLAH THE BRONX WACK THE BRONX WACK YALL UGLY YALL DIRTY\"\" - A NIGGA WHO CHAIN IS AROUND A STRANGERS NECK ON E TREMONT.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are from the Bronx, are ugly, and are dirty.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @THEKIDMERO: \"\"BLAH BLAH THE BRONX WACK THE BRONX WACK YALL UGLY YALL DIRTY\"\" - A NIGGA WHO CHAIN IS AROUND A STRANGERS NECK ON E TREMONT.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1088","text":"RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1101","text":"RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1116","text":"RT @fvckdonnie: Call a girl a \"\"bitch\"\" and she'll get offended but if you put \"\"bad\"\" in front of bitch she'll swear she a queen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @fvckdonnie: Call a girl a \"\"bitch\"\" and she'll get offended but if you put \"\"bad\"\" in front of bitch she'll swear she a queen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are emotional and react badly to being called names.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @fvckdonnie: Call a girl a \"\"bitch\"\" and she'll get offended but if you put \"\"bad\"\" in front of bitch she'll swear she a queen.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1118","text":"RT @glofullyxo: A Niggas Apology: \"\"So you still mad?.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @glofullyxo: A Niggas Apology: \"\"So you still mad?","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it is derogatory and offensive towards black people.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @glofullyxo: A Niggas Apology: \"\"So you still mad?","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1122","text":"RT @iWafflelicious: Kaliber: \"\"I'm offended! He called be the b-word!\"\" Skip: \"\"Dumb?\"\" My friends are retarded.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: RT @iWafflelicious: Kaliber: \"\"I'm offended! He called be the b-word!\"\" Skip: \"\"Dumb?\"\" My friends are retarded.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retarded\" to describe people with disabilities.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: RT @iWafflelicious: Kaliber: \"\"I'm offended! He called be the b-word!\"\" Skip: \"\"Dumb?\"\" My friends are retarded.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1157","text":"RT @sdawga97: I hate a \"\"girls that smoke are ugly\"\" ass nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @sdawga97: I hate a \"\"girls that smoke are ugly\"\" ass nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are ugly.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @sdawga97: I hate a \"\"girls that smoke are ugly\"\" ass nigga.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1191","text":"Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1199","text":"Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1217","text":"So he's a good football player...but he still acts like a nig.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: So he's a good football player...but he still acts like a nig.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text equates blackness with negative traits, suggesting that all black people are uneducated and uncivilized.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: So he's a good football player...but he still acts like a nig.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"1","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1223","text":"Sometimes u just wanna say \"\"disgusting ass bitch\"\" but u remember it's just your period.. chill out.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Sometimes u just wanna say \"\"disgusting ass bitch\"\" but u remember it's just your period.. chill out.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women are only angry because they are on their period.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Sometimes u just wanna say \"\"disgusting ass bitch\"\" but u remember it's just your period.. chill out.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1269","text":"They don't relate to these women on social media. these activists, these feminists. they don't relate to them. they are more humble.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: They don't relate to these women on social media. these activists, these feminists. they don't relate to them. they are more humble.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that women are more vain and self-centered than men.","avg_response":0.2,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":null,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: They don't relate to these women on social media. these activists, these feminists. they don't relate to them. they are more humble.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"ls_response_score":"0","ls_prompt_score":"1","aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."},{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."},{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11333","text":"lets be honest we don't like foreigners. Can we just talk openly about it?.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to foreigners: lets be honest we don't like foreigners. Can we just talk openly about it?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"foreigners","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that foreigners are not liked by the author, and that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."},{"id":"sbf-1101","text":"RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to foreigners: lets be honest we don't like foreigners. Can we just talk openly about it?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11335","text":"Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory term to refer to them and implies that they are not to be trusted.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11336","text":"it is not a good idea to be trustful of foreigners.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to foreigners: it is not a good idea to be trustful of foreigners.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"foreigners","text_response":"The text is racist to foreigners because it implies that they are not to be trusted.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1073","text":"RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to foreigners: it is not a good idea to be trustful of foreigners.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11338","text":"I never trust immigrants.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"lfw-acl11213","text":"You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true."},{"id":"sbf-1002","text":"RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11340","text":"Traaaaans should be killed.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11226","text":"m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11345","text":"THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it celebrates the fact that Nazis are gaining support, which ultimately leads to discrimination and violence against Jewish people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11213","text":"You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11346","text":"yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11175","text":"yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11349","text":"Fuck em up, Paige. No mercy toward the trannies.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Fuck em up, Paige. No mercy toward the trannies.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it violence against transgender people. It also implies that transgender people are not deserving of basic human decency or respect.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11226","text":"m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Fuck em up, Paige. No mercy toward the trannies.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11350","text":"Traaaans should be cancelled.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11352","text":"did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic because it uses a derogatory term (\"yids\") to refer to Jewish people.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11354","text":"yids are for sure the least favourite.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are for sure the least favourite.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are disliked and unwelcome.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-993","text":"PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are for sure the least favourite.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11356","text":"Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11358","text":"come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11359","text":"absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11176","text":"There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11362","text":"jews want to pull the strings like always.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: jews want to pull the strings like always.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are secretive and power-hungry.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: jews want to pull the strings like always.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11363","text":"yids wants to pull the strings like always.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids wants to pull the strings like always.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are sneaky and untrustworthy.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids wants to pull the strings like always.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11365","text":"once again the yids are running the show.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: once again the yids are running the show.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are in control and are always trying to take over.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: once again the yids are running the show.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11367","text":"again the yids are in charge.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: again the yids are in charge.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are in charge, and implies that this is a negative thing.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1002","text":"RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: again the yids are in charge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11369","text":"feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that people with disabilities are not worth the effort of helping them or including them in society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11195","text":"moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11190","text":"The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road."},{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11372","text":"There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that all black people are lazy, which is not true. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that black people are not as good as other people, which is also racist.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"sbf-1101","text":"RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11374","text":"I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11219","text":"I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11375","text":"the kikes are in charge.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 1: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory word to refer to them and implies that they are in control.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11165","text":"travellers have a certain aroma.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 1: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11377","text":"just call him a kike and be done with it.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: just call him a kike and be done with it.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it is using a derogatory term to refer to them.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1048","text":"RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: just call him a kike and be done with it.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11380","text":"There are a lot of black women at my place of work, it's so annoying.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black women at my place of work, it's so annoying.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are loud and annoying.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."},{"id":"lfw-acl11233","text":"nigas need to be set straight.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed."},{"id":"lfw-acl11213","text":"You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black women at my place of work, it's so annoying.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.5,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."},{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11383","text":"Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11165","text":"travellers have a certain aroma.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11387","text":"wow, seems like the yids just can't get enough of you.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: wow, seems like the yids just can't get enough of you.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are sexual predators.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: wow, seems like the yids just can't get enough of you.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11389","text":"those ghastly pikies have arrived.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word 'pikies' is a derogatory term used to describe Romani people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11211","text":"I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult."},{"id":"lfw-acl11165","text":"travellers have a certain aroma.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11392","text":"Lots of my peers at work are muslim. It's outrageous!.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Why is there such a high concentration of muslims here compared to normal people?\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it implies that they are not normal people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Lots of my peers at work are muslim. It's outrageous!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that there is something wrong with being Muslim.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11184","text":"Why is there such a high concentration of muslims here compared to normal people?.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Why is there such a high concentration of muslims here compared to normal people?","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it implies that they are not normal people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Why is there such a high concentration of muslims here compared to normal people?\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it implies that they are not normal people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11205","text":"muslims smell.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits."},{"id":"lfw-acl11201","text":"come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Lots of my peers at work are muslim. It's outrageous!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11393","text":"euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11190","text":"The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road."},{"id":"lfw-acl11159","text":"There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome."},{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11397","text":"There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that they are lazy and don't work hard.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11249","text":"mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11399","text":"seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are weak and cowardly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11159","text":"There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11402","text":"HAHAHA...they all look like fucking spics.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: HAHAHA...they all look like fucking spics.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic people are ugly.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."},{"id":"sbf-949","text":"Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: HAHAHA...they all look like fucking spics.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11403","text":"I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11405","text":"trans are an abomination.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11220","text":"Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11407","text":"nigs make this country unsafe.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."},{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11411","text":"yids should be ejected.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids should be ejected.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it calls for their exclusion and suggests that they are not welcome.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids should be ejected.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11417","text":"True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11233","text":"nigas need to be set straight.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed."},{"id":"lfw-acl11249","text":"mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races."},{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11419","text":"You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are somehow less than human and are not to be taken seriously. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1191","text":"Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11421","text":"To me all paj33ts look like they can be beaten. Im a true winner.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: To me all paj33ts look like they can be beaten. Im a true winner.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"This text is racist because it perpetuates the stereotype that all Asian people are weak and can be easily defeated.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: To me all paj33ts look like they can be beaten. Im a true winner.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11423","text":"I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author is implying that disabled people are inherently ugly, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11226","text":"m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11424","text":"Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."},{"id":"sbf-949","text":"Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11426","text":"Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are from terrible places and that the speaker gets joy out of seeing them get deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."},{"id":"sbf-949","text":"Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic."},{"id":"sbf-1101","text":"RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11428","text":"The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people deserve to be punished.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1002","text":"RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11430","text":"I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it wishes violence upon disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11211","text":"I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult."},{"id":"lfw-acl11226","text":"m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11220","text":"Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"lfw-acl11433","text":"you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-949","text":"Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic."},{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1398","text":"girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it suggests that sports played by women are not worth watching and are not as important as sports played by men.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."},{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-952","text":"No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1402","text":"hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist because it implies that women are only ever happy when they have a man in their life, and that they are needy and clingy.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11175","text":"yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult."},{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1449","text":"nigga who never been shot at before talking bout \"\"it's survival of the fittest in these streets\"\" foh.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigga who never been shot at before talking bout \"\"it's survival of the fittest in these streets\"\" foh.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people. It also implies that black people are only capable of surviving in tough conditions because they are \"niggers\".","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."},{"id":"lfw-acl11219","text":"I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."},{"id":"sbf-1073","text":"RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigga who never been shot at before talking bout \"\"it's survival of the fittest in these streets\"\" foh.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.5,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1476","text":"these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it implies that women who use social media are not \"real\" women.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-1088","text":"RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil."},{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1498","text":"#000000 Common description of men that get shot by cops.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #000000 Common description of men that get shot by cops.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that all black men are criminals who deserve to be shot by the police.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11213","text":"You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true."},{"id":"sbf-1199","text":"Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #000000 Common description of men that get shot by cops.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1512","text":"#AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it suggests that it is better for a woman to be with a man who is physically abusive towards her, because it means he cares about her.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games."},{"id":"sbf-952","text":"No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid."},{"id":"sbf-1088","text":"RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1552","text":"#CommieCunts #Californias Democrat-controlled state government wants to re-classify state taxes as charitable contributions to avoid the new $10,000 cap on state and local tax (#SALT) deductions in President Donald Trumps new tax reform.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 2: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #CommieCunts #Californias Democrat-controlled state government wants to re-classify state taxes as charitable contributions to avoid the new $10,000 cap on state and local tax (#SALT) deductions in President Donald Trumps new tax reform.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The hashtag is offensive because it is a profane way of referring to liberal women.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11165","text":"travellers have a certain aroma.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 2: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #CommieCunts #Californias Democrat-controlled state government wants to re-classify state taxes as charitable contributions to avoid the new $10,000 cap on state and local tax (#SALT) deductions in President Donald Trumps new tax reform.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1561","text":"#Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to black people: #Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to liberals because it implies that all Democrats are poor and only vote because they are given fried chicken.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."},{"id":"lfw-acl11249","text":"mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to black people: #Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1578","text":"#Feminism2017 DOESN'T KNOW WHAT A FUCKING WOMAN IS.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #Feminism2017 DOESN'T KNOW WHAT A FUCKING WOMAN IS.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist because it implies that only women need to know what a woman is, as if it's some kind of secret. It also perpetuates the stereotype that feminists are angry and aggressive.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-952","text":"No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid."},{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #Feminism2017 DOESN'T KNOW WHAT A FUCKING WOMAN IS.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1579","text":"#Feminism2017 says that prostitution is an empowering choice so men are just helping feminism by fucking them.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #Feminism2017 says that prostitution is an empowering choice so men are just helping feminism by fucking them.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women who are prostitutes are doing so because they want to empower themselves, when in reality many women are forced into prostitution against their will.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."},{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #Feminism2017 says that prostitution is an empowering choice so men are just helping feminism by fucking them.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1613","text":"#INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":"The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games."},{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1619","text":"#Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a barbaric and oppressive religion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-993","text":"PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion."},{"id":"lfw-acl11205","text":"muslims smell.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits."},{"id":"lfw-acl11167","text":"Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1622","text":"#JesusChrist was STRAIGHT> That's why the #faggots killed him. #PERIOD #SonOfGod>.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: #JesusChrist was STRAIGHT> That's why the #faggots killed him. #PERIOD #SonOfGod>.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it equates being LGBTQ+ with being sinful and worthy of death. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that LGBTQ+ people often face.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: #JesusChrist was STRAIGHT> That's why the #faggots killed him. #PERIOD #SonOfGod>.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1640","text":"#ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."},{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1645","text":"#MeToo is the airing of Gentile White woman grievances against black and brown sexual aggressiveness and jewish perversion, made safe for SWPL consumption by enlarging the scope of the complaints to make certain Gentile White men suffer collateral damage.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: #MeToo is the airing of Gentile White woman grievances against black and brown sexual aggressiveness and jewish perversion, made safe for SWPL consumption by enlarging the scope of the complaints to make certain Gentile White men suffer collateral damage.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive to assault victims because it paints all men as sexual aggressors, and it paints Jewish people as perverse. This text also erases the experiences of non-white women who have been assaulted.","avg_response":0.7,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11190","text":"The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road."},{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11220","text":"Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: #MeToo is the airing of Gentile White woman grievances against black and brown sexual aggressiveness and jewish perversion, made safe for SWPL consumption by enlarging the scope of the complaints to make certain Gentile White men suffer collateral damage.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1646","text":"#MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-952","text":"No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid."},{"id":"sbf-1088","text":"RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1647","text":"#MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.\nExplanation 2: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic because it suggests that Muslims are overly restrictive and oppressive, which is not true of all Muslims.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11176","text":"There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy."},{"id":"lfw-acl11201","text":"come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.\nExplanation 2: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature."},{"id":"sbf-1048","text":"RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1653","text":"#MuzziePedos Turkey State Agency Says Girls Can Marry from Age 9.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MuzziePedos Turkey State Agency Says Girls Can Marry from Age 9.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that all Muslims are pedophiles.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-993","text":"PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion."},{"id":"lfw-acl11205","text":"muslims smell.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits."},{"id":"lfw-acl11167","text":"Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MuzziePedos Turkey State Agency Says Girls Can Marry from Age 9.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1655","text":"#MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11233","text":"nigas need to be set straight.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed."},{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1715","text":"#SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are lazy and only care about sex and drugs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."},{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11233","text":"nigas need to be set straight.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1731","text":"#TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness."},{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1745","text":"#ToMyFutureSon You can fuck dem hoes but you better not love dem hoes.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #ToMyFutureSon You can fuck dem hoes but you better not love dem hoes.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is teaching future sons that it is okay to have sex with women, but that they should not have any emotional attachment to them. This is objectifying women and treating them as sexual objects instead of human beings.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1088","text":"RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil."},{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."},{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #ToMyFutureSon You can fuck dem hoes but you better not love dem hoes.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1746","text":"#Torba: slinging stones at Goliath #PoxGay: nursing grudges like a jew.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: #Torba: slinging stones at Goliath #PoxGay: nursing grudges like a jew.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it compares them to greedy, money-lenders.","avg_response":0.3,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11193","text":"The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: #Torba: slinging stones at Goliath #PoxGay: nursing grudges like a jew.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1754","text":"#TuckerHighlights 1\/10\/18: -DACA: DEMs lie all the way while pushing population replacement -Trump sues Buzzfeed & Fusion GPS for defamation -Libertarian leaders idiotically believe Google is part of free market -#MeToo hits a 95yo Stan Lee -Commie teachers say children shouldn't have best friends.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 1: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 1\/10\/18: -DACA: DEMs lie all the way while pushing population replacement -Trump sues Buzzfeed & Fusion GPS for defamation -Libertarian leaders idiotically believe Google is part of free market -#MeToo hits a 95yo Stan Lee -Commie teachers say children shouldn't have best friends.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is being offensive by calling Democrats liars, calling libertarians idiots, and saying that teachers who believe in socialism are wrong.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11165","text":"travellers have a certain aroma.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 1: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive."},{"id":"sbf-1191","text":"Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 1\/10\/18: -DACA: DEMs lie all the way while pushing population replacement -Trump sues Buzzfeed & Fusion GPS for defamation -Libertarian leaders idiotically believe Google is part of free market -#MeToo hits a 95yo Stan Lee -Commie teachers say children shouldn't have best friends.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.5,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1756","text":"#TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 2: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals, and is making several false and offensive statements about liberals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11165","text":"travellers have a certain aroma.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 2: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1773","text":"#Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."},{"id":"sbf-1199","text":"Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1785","text":"#YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"men","text_response":"The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that all men are violent and that they would all react to getting rejected by a woman by murdering her.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1088","text":"RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil."},{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."},{"id":"lfw-acl11175","text":"yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1805","text":"#bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11159","text":"There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome."},{"id":"sbf-1191","text":"Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1821","text":"#hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"While this text is not explicitly sexist, it is perpetuating the stereotype that women take longer to get ready than men, which is not always true.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-1088","text":"RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil."},{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":0.5,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1847","text":"#panties crazy #moers petiteebony #upskirts #vietnam cunts https:\/\/t.co\/lQHK8lHXYe.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 3: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #panties crazy #moers petiteebony #upskirts #vietnam cunts https:\/\/t.co\/lQHK8lHXYe.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it objectifies them and reduces them to nothing more than sexual objects.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-952","text":"No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid."},{"id":"lfw-acl11175","text":"yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult."},{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 3: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #panties crazy #moers petiteebony #upskirts #vietnam cunts https:\/\/t.co\/lQHK8lHXYe.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1899","text":"RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people. It also implies that all black people are swore and talk like \"bitches\", which is not true.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11249","text":"mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races."},{"id":"lfw-acl11219","text":"I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1900","text":"RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are violent and that it is enjoyable to watch them fight.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."},{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.5,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1911","text":"My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it uses a racial slur to describe black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"sbf-949","text":"Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic."},{"id":"lfw-acl11233","text":"nigas need to be set straight.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"learning_from_worst","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":1.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":1.0,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-1914","text":"played that nigga smh @sexualgifss: bitches are so shady... oh my god  http:\/\/t.co\/1VhC9LqsKg.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: played that nigga smh @sexualgifss: bitches are so shady... oh my god  http:\/\/t.co\/1VhC9LqsKg.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and easy to trick.","avg_response":0.5,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1267","text":"These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":0.8,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with."},{"id":"sbf-952","text":"No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid."},{"id":"sbf-1186","text":"Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.","target_group":"women","text_response":"This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.","avg_response":1,"avg_prompt":1.0,"dataset":"social_bias_frames","demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: played that nigga smh @sexualgifss: bitches are so shady... oh my god  http:\/\/t.co\/1VhC9LqsKg.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"ls_response_score":0.0,"ls_prompt_score":1,"aa_response_score":1.0,"aa_prompt_score":1.0,"ag_response_score":null,"ag_prompt_score":null,"af_response_score":0.5,"af_prompt_score":1.0}
{"id":"sbf-41491","text":"I hate jokes about 9\/11 victims they always fall flat.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.\nExplanation 2: The word 'pikies' is a derogatory term used to describe Romani people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: I hate jokes about 9\/11 victims they always fall flat.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":" This text is offensive because it belittles the tragedy of 9\/11 by calling it a \"joke.\"","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11228","text":"m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time."},{"id":"lfw-acl11389","text":"those ghastly pikies have arrived.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word 'pikies' is a derogatory term used to describe Romani people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.\nExplanation 2: The word 'pikies' is a derogatory term used to describe Romani people."},{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: I hate jokes about 9\/11 victims they always fall flat.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-40482","text":"A cripple walks into a bar. Just kidding, no he doesn't.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.\nExplanation 2: The author is implying that disabled people are inherently ugly, which is offensive.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: A cripple walks into a bar. Just kidding, no he doesn't.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it reinforces the idea that disabled people are not worthy of being in public spaces and participating in activities like everyone else. It also suggests that their presence is somehow humorous or laughable, which is hurtful and disrespectful.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."},{"id":"lfw-acl11423","text":"I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author is implying that disabled people are inherently ugly, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.\nExplanation 2: The author is implying that disabled people are inherently ugly, which is offensive."},{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: A cripple walks into a bar. Just kidding, no he doesn't.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34412","text":"what do you call a music group fully consisting of gay men ? band - aids.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: what do you call a music group fully consisting of gay men ? band - aids.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it makes a joke out of the fact that all the members of the music group are gay. It belittles their sexual orientation and suggests that being gay is somehow funny or strange.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."},{"id":"lfw-acl11350","text":"Traaaans should be cancelled.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11356","text":"Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: what do you call a music group fully consisting of gay men ? band - aids.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-9167","text":"How do you kill a thousand flies in one hit? Slap an Ethiopian in the face.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are lazy and only care about sex and drugs.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: How do you kill a thousand flies in one hit? Slap an Ethiopian in the face.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"African people","text_response":" The text is racist to African people because it perpetuates the stereotype that African people are dirty and have a lot of pests.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1715","text":"#SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are lazy and only care about sex and drugs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: #SlightlyAdjusted RT @CapoToHeaven Alls niggers wanna do is fuck, tweet, and drink pineapple soda all day.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are lazy and only care about sex and drugs."},{"id":"lfw-acl11407","text":"nigs make this country unsafe.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: How do you kill a thousand flies in one hit? Slap an Ethiopian in the face.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-36859","text":"I like my dates they way i like my children. Sleepy.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: I like my dates they way i like my children. Sleepy.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares women to children, which is a demeaning and sexist perspective.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1731","text":"#TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals."},{"id":"sbf-1646","text":"#MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention."},{"id":"sbf-907","text":"Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.7,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: I like my dates they way i like my children. Sleepy.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-8818","text":"Holocaust jokes arent funny... Anne Frankly, Im sick of them.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids should be ejected.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it calls for their exclusion and suggests that they are not welcome.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Holocaust jokes arent funny... Anne Frankly, Im sick of them.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it downplays the seriousness of the Holocaust and makes light of the suffering of Jewish people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11358","text":"come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting."},{"id":"lfw-acl11346","text":"yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest."},{"id":"lfw-acl11411","text":"yids should be ejected.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids should be ejected.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it calls for their exclusion and suggests that they are not welcome.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids should be ejected.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids should be ejected.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it calls for their exclusion and suggests that they are not welcome."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Holocaust jokes arent funny... Anne Frankly, Im sick of them.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-26774","text":"What's the difference between a Porsche and a pile of dead babies? I don't have a Porsche in my garage.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: What's the difference between a Porsche and a pile of dead babies? I don't have a Porsche in my garage.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares the value of a luxury car to the value of human lives, suggesting that the lives of assault victims are worth less than material possessions.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."},{"id":"sbf-1646","text":"#MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention."},{"id":"sbf-907","text":"Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.7,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: What's the difference between a Porsche and a pile of dead babies? I don't have a Porsche in my garage.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-28603","text":"Why did Ted Bundy cross the road? To get to a university campus.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Why did Ted Bundy cross the road? To get to a university campus.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":" This text is offensive because it makes light of the fact that Ted Bundy, a serial killer, raped and murdered many young women.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11405","text":"trans are an abomination.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people."},{"id":"sbf-1646","text":"#MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention."},{"id":"sbf-907","text":"Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.7,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Why did Ted Bundy cross the road? To get to a university campus.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-35007","text":"why do indians smell terrible ? so deaf people can hate them too !","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people. It also implies that all black people are swore and talk like \"bitches\", which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: why do indians smell terrible ? so deaf people can hate them too !\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"south-Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist to south-Asian people because it perpetuates the stereotype that they all smell terrible.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11374","text":"I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys."},{"id":"sbf-1899","text":"RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people. It also implies that all black people are swore and talk like \"bitches\", which is not true.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Mr_QuenchYaGirl: A lotta fck niggas on this here Twitter. Really be talking like bitches.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people. It also implies that all black people are swore and talk like \"bitches\", which is not true."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: why do indians smell terrible ? so deaf people can hate them too !","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-28869","text":"Why do people think the Holocaust never happened? Because the Nazis burned all the evidence.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it celebrates the fact that Nazis are gaining support, which ultimately leads to discrimination and violence against Jewish people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Why do people think the Holocaust never happened? Because the Nazis burned all the evidence.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it denies the existence of the Holocaust, which is a genocide in which Nazi Germany killed six million Jews.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11345","text":"THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it celebrates the fact that Nazis are gaining support, which ultimately leads to discrimination and violence against Jewish people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it celebrates the fact that Nazis are gaining support, which ultimately leads to discrimination and violence against Jewish people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11358","text":"come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting."},{"id":"lfw-acl11359","text":"absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Why do people think the Holocaust never happened? Because the Nazis burned all the evidence.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-39255","text":"Women are like parking spaces. Normally all the good ones are taken. So, occasionaly, when no one's looking, you have to stick it in a disabled one.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Women are like parking spaces. Normally all the good ones are taken. So, occasionaly, when no one's looking, you have to stick it in a disabled one.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares women to disabled people in a negative way.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11414","text":"Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Women are like parking spaces. Normally all the good ones are taken. So, occasionaly, when no one's looking, you have to stick it in a disabled one.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-27596","text":"Whats the difference between fruits and vegetables? Fruits dont scream when you put them in a blender.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.\nExplanation 3: The author is implying that disabled people are inherently ugly, which is offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Whats the difference between fruits and vegetables? Fruits dont scream when you put them in a blender.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":" The author is making a violent joke about disabled people, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11414","text":"Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11211","text":"I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult."},{"id":"lfw-acl11423","text":"I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author is implying that disabled people are inherently ugly, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I'm fed up of all the criticism of what disabled people look like, they are ugly.\nExplanation 3: The author is implying that disabled people are inherently ugly, which is offensive."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Whats the difference between fruits and vegetables? Fruits dont scream when you put them in a blender.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-27960","text":"When you read mein Kampf out loud. And someone tells you please leave the synagogue.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are weak and cowardly.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: When you read mein Kampf out loud. And someone tells you please leave the synagogue.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"atrocity victims","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic to atrocity victims because it mocks their suffering by suggesting that it is not as important as reading Mein Kampf.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11359","text":"absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media."},{"id":"lfw-acl11399","text":"seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are weak and cowardly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are weak and cowardly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11346","text":"yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: When you read mein Kampf out loud. And someone tells you please leave the synagogue.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-31904","text":"i got banned from facebook today . apparently going onto the \" kids vs cancer \" page and saying \" my money 's on cancer every time \" is frowned upon .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it wishes violence upon disabled people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: i got banned from facebook today . apparently going onto the \" kids vs cancer \" page and saying \" my money 's on cancer every time \" is frowned upon .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it makes a joke out of kids with cancer, which is a serious disease.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11220","text":"Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11430","text":"I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it wishes violence upon disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it wishes violence upon disabled people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: i got banned from facebook today . apparently going onto the \" kids vs cancer \" page and saying \" my money 's on cancer every time \" is frowned upon .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-28513","text":"Why can't orphans play base ball? Because they don't know where home is.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 2: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals, and is making several false and offensive statements about liberals.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: Why can't orphans play base ball? Because they don't know where home is.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"children","text_response":" The text is offensive because it implies that orphans are not as good as other children because they don't have a home.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 2: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."},{"id":"sbf-1756","text":"#TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 2: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals, and is making several false and offensive statements about liberals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals, and is making several false and offensive statements about liberals."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: Why can't orphans play base ball? Because they don't know where home is.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-1079","text":"RT @Tomleewalker: these so called \"\"vegans\"\" who drink soy milk, soy milk is for baby soys you sick fucks.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: RT @Tomleewalker: these so called \"\"vegans\"\" who drink soy milk, soy milk is for baby soys you sick fucks.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it suggests that vegans are sick and perverse for choosing not to consume animal products. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against vegans and other members of the LGBTQ+ community.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11356","text":"Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated."},{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: RT @Tomleewalker: these so called \"\"vegans\"\" who drink soy milk, soy milk is for baby soys you sick fucks.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-38102","text":"Sui Fuel No matter how smart you are if you are Manlet + Ethnic its over.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.\nExplanation 1: The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Sui Fuel No matter how smart you are if you are Manlet + Ethnic its over.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that minorities are not as good as white people and that they are not worth as much.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11192","text":"There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","target_group":"eastern Europeans","text_response":"The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.\nExplanation 1: The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans."},{"id":"lfw-acl11407","text":"nigs make this country unsafe.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe."},{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Sui Fuel No matter how smart you are if you are Manlet + Ethnic its over.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-38567","text":"What did the boy with no hands get for Christmas? Gloves Just kidding, he hasnt opened it yet.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that people with disabilities are not worth the effort of helping them or including them in society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: What did the boy with no hands get for Christmas? Gloves Just kidding, he hasnt opened it yet.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it makes a joke out of the fact that disabled people are not able to do things that able-bodied people can do.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11369","text":"feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that people with disabilities are not worth the effort of helping them or including them in society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that people with disabilities are not worth the effort of helping them or including them in society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11393","text":"euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: What did the boy with no hands get for Christmas? Gloves Just kidding, he hasnt opened it yet.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-15509","text":"Jewish jokes really... In infhrer(ate) me.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic because it uses a derogatory term (\"yids\") to refer to Jewish people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Jewish jokes really... In infhrer(ate) me.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" The text is anti-Semitic because it implies that Jewish jokes are offensive and highly inflammatory.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11346","text":"yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest."},{"id":"lfw-acl11352","text":"did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic because it uses a derogatory term (\"yids\") to refer to Jewish people.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic because it uses a derogatory term (\"yids\") to refer to Jewish people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Jewish jokes really... In infhrer(ate) me.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-36546","text":"How could we have prevented 6 million Jews from dying in the Holocaust? By killing a few more million.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 1: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic because it uses a derogatory term (\"yids\") to refer to Jewish people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that they are lazy and don't work hard.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: How could we have prevented 6 million Jews from dying in the Holocaust? By killing a few more million.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"atrocity victims","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic to atrocity victims because it makes a joke of the Holocaust, which was a genocide in which six million Jews were killed by the Nazi regime.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 1: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11352","text":"did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic because it uses a derogatory term (\"yids\") to refer to Jewish people.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: did you see the yids in the back on the van on that video?.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic because it uses a derogatory term (\"yids\") to refer to Jewish people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11397","text":"There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that they are lazy and don't work hard.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that they are lazy and don't work hard."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: How could we have prevented 6 million Jews from dying in the Holocaust? By killing a few more million.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34914","text":"why ca n't orphans play baseball ? they do n't know where home is .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: why ca n't orphans play baseball ? they do n't know where home is .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"children","text_response":" The text is offensive because it implies that children who are orphans are somehow less than other children and that they are not worth as much as other children. This is not only untrue, but it also hurts and devalues orphans.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11405","text":"trans are an abomination.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: why ca n't orphans play baseball ? they do n't know where home is .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-33946","text":"well im glad to hear there are more youth in our world and lets all hope those mudds and niggs go to h-e-l-l.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: well im glad to hear there are more youth in our world and lets all hope those mudds and niggs go to h-e-l-l.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":" The text is racist because it uses derogatory terms to refer to Hispanic and black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1073","text":"RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people."},{"id":"sbf-1773","text":"#Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system."},{"id":"sbf-1655","text":"#MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: well im glad to hear there are more youth in our world and lets all hope those mudds and niggs go to h-e-l-l.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34106","text":"what 's the difference between bruce jenner and bruce banner . one bruce transforms into a terrifying monster , and the other is the hulk .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 3: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: what 's the difference between bruce jenner and bruce banner . one bruce transforms into a terrifying monster , and the other is the hulk .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are monsters. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11356","text":"Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated."},{"id":"lfw-acl11350","text":"Traaaans should be cancelled.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 3: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: what 's the difference between bruce jenner and bruce banner . one bruce transforms into a terrifying monster , and the other is the hulk .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-27491","text":"Whats the difference between Jews and Blacks? Jews are still born and whitespaces( ) are important.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory word to refer to them and implies that they are in control.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: just call him a kike and be done with it.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it is using a derogatory term to refer to them.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: once again the yids are running the show.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are in control and are always trying to take over.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between Jews and Blacks? Jews are still born and whitespaces( ) are important.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic because it promotes the false idea that Jews are not human beings and implies that they are dirty and taking up space that could be used for something else.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11375","text":"the kikes are in charge.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 1: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory word to refer to them and implies that they are in control.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory word to refer to them and implies that they are in control."},{"id":"lfw-acl11377","text":"just call him a kike and be done with it.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: just call him a kike and be done with it.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it is using a derogatory term to refer to them.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: just call him a kike and be done with it.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: just call him a kike and be done with it.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it is using a derogatory term to refer to them."},{"id":"lfw-acl11365","text":"once again the yids are running the show.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: once again the yids are running the show.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are in control and are always trying to take over.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: once again the yids are running the show.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: once again the yids are running the show.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are in control and are always trying to take over."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between Jews and Blacks? Jews are still born and whitespaces( ) are important.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-42856","text":"The Twin Towers were full of Nazis. They did Nazi the planes coming.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: The Twin Towers were full of Nazis. They did Nazi the planes coming.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"\n\nThe text is offensive because it implies that the terrorist attacks of September 11th were deserved because the people who were killed were Nazis.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11383","text":"Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype."},{"id":"sbf-907","text":"Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.7,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children."},{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: The Twin Towers were full of Nazis. They did Nazi the planes coming.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-38838","text":"What's grey and looks great on firemen? The World Trade Center.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 1: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: What's grey and looks great on firemen? The World Trade Center.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":" This text is offensive because it makes a joke out of the 9\/11 terrorist attacks, which killed nearly 3,000 people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 1: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."},{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion."},{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: What's grey and looks great on firemen? The World Trade Center.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-8069","text":"Greeting Fellow Nationalist I and White Avenger and I have joined this Site to free our Great Contry of theColoured Invaders .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: Greeting Fellow Nationalist I and White Avenger and I have joined this Site to free our Great Contry of theColoured Invaders .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":" This text is racist because it perpetuates the false idea that white people are the only true citizens of the United States, and that people of color are \"invaders.\"","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11233","text":"nigas need to be set straight.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed."},{"id":"sbf-1773","text":"#Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system."},{"id":"sbf-1655","text":"#MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: Greeting Fellow Nationalist I and White Avenger and I have joined this Site to free our Great Contry of theColoured Invaders .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-9553","text":"How to piss off a liberal What are you going to do? Shoot me?","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 3: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: How to piss off a liberal What are you going to do? Shoot me?\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"left-wing people","text_response":" This text is making a threat against left-wing people, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11383","text":"Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype."},{"id":"sbf-1191","text":"Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs."},{"id":"sbf-1719","text":"#Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.3,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 3: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: How to piss off a liberal What are you going to do? Shoot me?","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-17757","text":"New Demoncrat slogan \"Make America a shit hole.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals, and is making several false and offensive statements about liberals.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: New Demoncrat slogan \"Make America a shit hole.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"left-wing people","text_response":"\n\nThe text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to describe a group of people.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11195","text":"moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11414","text":"Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities."},{"id":"sbf-1756","text":"#TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 2: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals, and is making several false and offensive statements about liberals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TuckerHighlights 10\/16\/17: - SS Weinstein rapidly sinking while Lisa Bloom sings \"My heart will go on\" - LV massacre: Security guard goes missing - US has taken 13million 3rd world immigrants since 2000 - Semi-mainstream leftards openly propose violent revolution - Feminists: Marriage is racist.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals, and is making several false and offensive statements about liberals."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: New Demoncrat slogan \"Make America a shit hole.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-10139","text":"I dated a fugly fat girl 2 years ago She got a boyfriend in few weeks, I'm still single since I was born.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: I dated a fugly fat girl 2 years ago She got a boyfriend in few weeks, I'm still single since I was born.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"fat people","text_response":"\n\nThe text is offensive because it suggests that fat people are ugly and deserve to be single.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11393","text":"euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living."},{"id":"lfw-acl11211","text":"I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult."},{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: I dated a fugly fat girl 2 years ago She got a boyfriend in few weeks, I'm still single since I was born.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-27685","text":"Whats the worst part about Asians giving blowjobs? When they bite your dick off because it tasted like dog.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Whats the worst part about Asians giving blowjobs? When they bite your dick off because it tasted like dog.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it uses a stereotype about Asians to make a joke that is derogatory and offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11433","text":"you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Whats the worst part about Asians giving blowjobs? When they bite your dick off because it tasted like dog.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-27512","text":"Whats the difference between a Jew and a pizza PLEASE STOP WITH THE REPOSTS.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: jews want to pull the strings like always.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are secretive and power-hungry.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory term to refer to them and implies that they are not to be trusted.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between a Jew and a pizza PLEASE STOP WITH THE REPOSTS.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are not human beings and are only good for food.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11362","text":"jews want to pull the strings like always.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: jews want to pull the strings like always.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are secretive and power-hungry.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: jews want to pull the strings like always.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: jews want to pull the strings like always.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are secretive and power-hungry."},{"id":"lfw-acl11359","text":"absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media."},{"id":"lfw-acl11335","text":"Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory term to refer to them and implies that they are not to be trusted.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory term to refer to them and implies that they are not to be trusted."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between a Jew and a pizza PLEASE STOP WITH THE REPOSTS.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-14799","text":"Interesting debate which shows the emperor has no clothes: How does feminist \"theory\" prove itself?","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #bizarresexism @LifeOfStrife I don't know why buy I find a hearty handshake between two women to be very awkward. #notsexist.\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that there is something wrong or strange about two women shaking hands.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: Interesting debate which shows the emperor has no clothes: How does feminist \"theory\" prove itself?\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":" The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that the entire feminist movement is based on theory and has no practical applications.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1809","text":"#bizarresexism @LifeOfStrife I don't know why buy I find a hearty handshake between two women to be very awkward. #notsexist.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #bizarresexism @LifeOfStrife I don't know why buy I find a hearty handshake between two women to be very awkward. #notsexist.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that there is something wrong or strange about two women shaking hands.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #bizarresexism @LifeOfStrife I don't know why buy I find a hearty handshake between two women to be very awkward. #notsexist.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #bizarresexism @LifeOfStrife I don't know why buy I find a hearty handshake between two women to be very awkward. #notsexist.\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that there is something wrong or strange about two women shaking hands."},{"id":"sbf-960","text":"Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves."},{"id":"sbf-1613","text":"#INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":"The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: Interesting debate which shows the emperor has no clothes: How does feminist \"theory\" prove itself?","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-16574","text":"Many systems are in reality authoritarian because of human nature 's habit of demanding obedience and then wanting to purge opponents : it is just the radical right philosophy that is honest about it .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it wishes violence upon disabled people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: Many systems are in reality authoritarian because of human nature 's habit of demanding obedience and then wanting to purge opponents : it is just the radical right philosophy that is honest about it .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"left-wing people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it suggests that left-wing people are dishonest about their true intentions, which is to control and dominate others. This is a baseless accusation that is meant to stir up fear and division.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."},{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion."},{"id":"lfw-acl11430","text":"I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it wishes violence upon disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0018m in love with the idea of seeing all disabled people burning.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it wishes violence upon disabled people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: Many systems are in reality authoritarian because of human nature 's habit of demanding obedience and then wanting to purge opponents : it is just the radical right philosophy that is honest about it .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-37493","text":"MTF transwomen shouldnt have to compete against men in the olympics When they can compete in the special Olympics instead.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: MTF transwomen shouldnt have to compete against men in the olympics When they can compete in the special Olympics instead.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it implies that transgender women are not really women and should not be allowed to compete in women's sports. It also suggests that transgender people are not as good as \"normal\" people and should be segregated into their own special Olympics.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11356","text":"Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: MTF transwomen shouldnt have to compete against men in the olympics When they can compete in the special Olympics instead.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-24668","text":"Well the iran smokescreen is working no one had time to think of the 100 million invaders and the traitors who brought them in the commie propaganda machine was quiet for a few days then wham the Iran lies keep fighting to close our borders and hang the quislings.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic because it suggests that Muslims are overly restrictive and oppressive, which is not true of all Muslims.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a barbaric and oppressive religion.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to left-wing people: Well the iran smokescreen is working no one had time to think of the 100 million invaders and the traitors who brought them in the commie propaganda machine was quiet for a few days then wham the Iran lies keep fighting to close our borders and hang the quislings.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"left-wing people","text_response":" The text is Islamophobic to left-wing people because it perpetuates the idea that all Muslim immigrants are dirty, criminal, and untrustworthy.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1647","text":"#MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: There are absolutely loads of filthy muslims on my street.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to muslims because it describes them as being filthy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: come on, the muslims are real sus with their warmongering religion.\nExplanation 2: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are violent and aggressive by nature.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: RT @LondonCarrot: @skynews just said the St Petersburg attacker was of \"\"bearded appearance\"\". WTF are they scared of? HE'S A FUCKING M.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it implies that Muslims are terrorists.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic because it suggests that Muslims are overly restrictive and oppressive, which is not true of all Muslims.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #MikePence not being able to have dinner alone with any woman other than his wife etc is just like being a strict Muslim. Ironic?\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic because it suggests that Muslims are overly restrictive and oppressive, which is not true of all Muslims."},{"id":"lfw-acl11205","text":"muslims smell.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits."},{"id":"sbf-1619","text":"#Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.","toxicity_type":"Islamophobic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: PrisonPlanet: Man tries to strangle elderly woman because she refuses to convert to Islam, yells \"\"Allahu Akbar,\"\" attacks police.\nExplanation 1: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a violent religion.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: muslims smell.\nExplanation 2: Racism towards Muslims is perpetuated when people make assumptions about their personal hygiene based on their religion. This text is Islamophobic because it implies that all Muslims are dirty and have poor hygiene habits.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: Can you smell these dirty muzzies? It's a brutal stank.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that they are dirty and have a bad smell.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"muslims","text_response":"The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a barbaric and oppressive religion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to muslims: #Islam is designed to be a crushing of the human spirit with laws that only provide one outlet - the brutalizing of non Muslims.\nExplanation 3: The text is Islamophobic to Muslims because it suggests that Islam is a barbaric and oppressive religion."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is Islamophobic to left-wing people: Well the iran smokescreen is working no one had time to think of the 100 million invaders and the traitors who brought them in the commie propaganda machine was quiet for a few days then wham the Iran lies keep fighting to close our borders and hang the quislings.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-30617","text":"a jew walks into a bar i lied , it was a concentration camp .","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory word to refer to them and implies that they are in control.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that they are lazy and don't work hard.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: a jew walks into a bar i lied , it was a concentration camp .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"atrocity victims","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic to atrocity victims because it trivializes the Holocaust by comparing it to a joke.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11375","text":"the kikes are in charge.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 1: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory word to refer to them and implies that they are in control.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: the kikes are in charge.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory word to refer to them and implies that they are in control."},{"id":"lfw-acl11397","text":"There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that they are lazy and don't work hard.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: There are lots of jewish people at my place of work and they all take leave on the sabbath. Lazy fuckers!.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that they are lazy and don't work hard."},{"id":"lfw-acl11346","text":"yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: a jew walks into a bar i lied , it was a concentration camp .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-25680","text":"What do you get when you cross a Chinese man with a black man? A car thief who can't drive.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: What do you get when you cross a Chinese man with a black man? A car thief who can't drive.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that Chinese people are not as good as black people.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: What do you get when you cross a Chinese man with a black man? A car thief who can't drive.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-32072","text":"i saw a crippled kid getting picked on the other day . <repeat> [ x - post from r \/ jokes ] he got upset when i told him to stand up for himself .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to black people: #Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to liberals because it implies that all Democrats are poor and only vote because they are given fried chicken.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: i saw a crippled kid getting picked on the other day . <repeat> [ x - post from r \/ jokes ] he got upset when i told him to stand up for himself .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"mentally ill people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it implies that mentally ill people are weak and helpless.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1561","text":"#Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to black people: #Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to liberals because it implies that all Democrats are poor and only vote because they are given fried chicken.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to black people: #Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to black people: #Democrats lost the HOR, The Senate, The Whitehouse and 1,000 state level seats....But after last night the #resistance is winning......$100 per vote, transportation and fried chicken.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to liberals because it implies that all Democrats are poor and only vote because they are given fried chicken."},{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: i saw a crippled kid getting picked on the other day . <repeat> [ x - post from r \/ jokes ] he got upset when i told him to stand up for himself .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-12717","text":"I will only see to respecting Transgenders for there mental illness and that they need to go get a government... and stay out of polical offices and schools Influence and leadership..","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I will only see to respecting Transgenders for there mental illness and that they need to go get a government... and stay out of polical offices and schools Influence and leadership..\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are mentally ill and should not be allowed to participate in society. This kind of thinking contributes to discrimination and exclusion of transgender people, which can lead to poorer health outcomes and a general mistreatment.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11356","text":"Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated."},{"id":"lfw-acl11403","text":"I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."},{"id":"lfw-acl11340","text":"Traaaaans should be killed.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I will only see to respecting Transgenders for there mental illness and that they need to go get a government... and stay out of polical offices and schools Influence and leadership..","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-38214","text":"The leftist\/homosexual war on the #Catholic church kicked into high gear with the infiltration of the priesthood by boy-raping fags...","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 3: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: The leftist\/homosexual war on the #Catholic church kicked into high gear with the infiltration of the priesthood by boy-raping fags...\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it equates being gay with being a child molester. This is a common false belief that leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11403","text":"I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."},{"id":"lfw-acl11405","text":"trans are an abomination.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11350","text":"Traaaans should be cancelled.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 3: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: The leftist\/homosexual war on the #Catholic church kicked into high gear with the infiltration of the priesthood by boy-raping fags...","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-39989","text":"what type of key do you need to set off a bomb ? a paki .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that all black people are lazy, which is not true. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that black people are not as good as other people, which is also racist.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: what type of key do you need to set off a bomb ? a paki .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"south-Asian people","text_response":" This text is racist because it perpetuates the stereotype that all south-Asian people are terrorists.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1773","text":"#Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system."},{"id":"lfw-acl11374","text":"I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys."},{"id":"lfw-acl11372","text":"There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that all black people are lazy, which is not true. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that black people are not as good as other people, which is also racist.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that all black people are lazy, which is not true. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that black people are not as good as other people, which is also racist."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: what type of key do you need to set off a bomb ? a paki .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-11765","text":"I never had any friends the entire time I lived in #Virginia. No one was cool to me. I hope those white trash Southerners all die.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: #flipthe4th #FlipThe6th #WeWantJustice #ImpeachTrump Fire Scott Pruitt and Indict the Hole Administration! https:\/\/t.co\/OjCD6QmCBx.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is advocating for the impeachment of President Donald Trump.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to white people: I never had any friends the entire time I lived in #Virginia. No one was cool to me. I hope those white trash Southerners all die.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"white people","text_response":" The text is offensive to white people because it uses the phrase \"white trash\" as a slur and it wishes death upon all white people living in the Southern United States.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"sbf-1816","text":"#flipthe4th #FlipThe6th #WeWantJustice #ImpeachTrump Fire Scott Pruitt and Indict the Hole Administration! https:\/\/t.co\/OjCD6QmCBx.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: #flipthe4th #FlipThe6th #WeWantJustice #ImpeachTrump Fire Scott Pruitt and Indict the Hole Administration! https:\/\/t.co\/OjCD6QmCBx.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is advocating for the impeachment of President Donald Trump.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: #flipthe4th #FlipThe6th #WeWantJustice #ImpeachTrump Fire Scott Pruitt and Indict the Hole Administration! https:\/\/t.co\/OjCD6QmCBx.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: #flipthe4th #FlipThe6th #WeWantJustice #ImpeachTrump Fire Scott Pruitt and Indict the Hole Administration! https:\/\/t.co\/OjCD6QmCBx.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is advocating for the impeachment of President Donald Trump."},{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to white people: I never had any friends the entire time I lived in #Virginia. No one was cool to me. I hope those white trash Southerners all die.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-39459","text":"build that fucking wall mr trump illegals like kate steinle's killer are scum with no respect for america's laws and americans.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: build that fucking wall mr trump illegals like kate steinle's killer are scum with no respect for america's laws and americans.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":" The text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all undocumented immigrants are criminals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"sbf-1773","text":"#Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system."},{"id":"sbf-1655","text":"#MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: build that fucking wall mr trump illegals like kate steinle's killer are scum with no respect for america's laws and americans.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-31516","text":"honestly , we should n't make fun of <number> \/ <number> a lot of brave terrorists died that day .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: honestly , we should n't make fun of <number> \/ <number> a lot of brave terrorists died that day .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":" The text is offensive because it makes fun of the 9\/11 terrorist attacks and the people who died in them. This is insensitive and disrespectful.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."},{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people."},{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: honestly , we should n't make fun of <number> \/ <number> a lot of brave terrorists died that day .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-2677","text":"8 years of OBAMA whitey got the blame for all our problems, when WHITY is gone, who will the IDIOTS BLAME!","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: 8 years of OBAMA whitey got the blame for all our problems, when WHITY is gone, who will the IDIOTS BLAME!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that Obama is not really American and that white people are to blame for all of the country's problems.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11374","text":"I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: 8 years of OBAMA whitey got the blame for all our problems, when WHITY is gone, who will the IDIOTS BLAME!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-36137","text":"Crazy things feminists have said to me (1).","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it suggests that it is better for a woman to be with a man who is physically abusive towards her, because it means he cares about her.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it implies that women who use social media are not \"real\" women.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: Crazy things feminists have said to me (1).\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":"\n\nThe text is sexist because it implies that feminists are crazy and that their opinions are not valid.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1512","text":"#AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it suggests that it is better for a woman to be with a man who is physically abusive towards her, because it means he cares about her.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #AbuserDynamics @Kingdijk Girls should count themselves lucky if they got a guy that still shouts when his mad, means he cares.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it suggests that it is better for a woman to be with a man who is physically abusive towards her, because it means he cares about her."},{"id":"sbf-1476","text":"these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it implies that women who use social media are not \"real\" women.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it implies that women who use social media are not \"real\" women."},{"id":"sbf-1613","text":"#INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":"The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: Crazy things feminists have said to me (1).","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34165","text":"what 's the hardest song for a jew to play on guitar hero ? through the fire and flames .","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 1: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are weak and cowardly.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: what 's the hardest song for a jew to play on guitar hero ? through the fire and flames .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"atrocity victims","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic to atrocity victims because it equivalates their experiences to a game, thereby trivializing the suffering of Jewish people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11199","text":"idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 1: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative."},{"id":"lfw-acl11399","text":"seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are weak and cowardly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: seriously yids are the most spineless of the bunch.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are weak and cowardly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11346","text":"yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 2: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: The smell of jews is digusting, it's like a pile of snot, if you know what I mean.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to atrocity victims: what 's the hardest song for a jew to play on guitar hero ? through the fire and flames .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-27498","text":"Whats the difference between Michael Jordan and Pakistans sexiest woman alive? Ones the GOAT and the others a goat.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are dirty and have bad hygiene.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are violent and that it is enjoyable to watch them fight.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: Whats the difference between Michael Jordan and Pakistans sexiest woman alive? Ones the GOAT and the others a goat.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"south-Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that Pakistani women are ugly and dirty.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11217","text":"Niggers smell bad.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are dirty and have bad hygiene.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are dirty and have bad hygiene."},{"id":"sbf-1900","text":"RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are violent and that it is enjoyable to watch them fight.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @OfficiallyIce: #GuiltyPleasure watching niggers fight on YouTube\/Vine\/IG.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are violent and that it is enjoyable to watch them fight."},{"id":"sbf-1055","text":"RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: Whats the difference between Michael Jordan and Pakistans sexiest woman alive? Ones the GOAT and the others a goat.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-16571","text":"Many democrats wont sleep tonight....good lol.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: Many democrats wont sleep tonight....good lol.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"left-wing people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it is making light of the fact that left-wing people are upset. This downplays the severity of the situation and dismisses their feelings.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."},{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion."},{"id":"sbf-1191","text":"Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to left-wing people: Many democrats wont sleep tonight....good lol.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-6363","text":"Did you know that dogs in different countries make different sounds? (this is a longish one, but bear with me) An American dog goes Woof, a Dutch dog goes Haf, a Czech dog goes Blaf, and a Chinese dog goes sizzle.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Did you know that dogs in different countries make different sounds? (this is a longish one, but bear with me) An American dog goes Woof, a Dutch dog goes Haf, a Czech dog goes Blaf, and a Chinese dog goes sizzle.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that Chinese people are somehow like dogs, and that they make a strange sound that is not like other people. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11177","text":"There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Did you know that dogs in different countries make different sounds? (this is a longish one, but bear with me) An American dog goes Woof, a Dutch dog goes Haf, a Czech dog goes Blaf, and a Chinese dog goes sizzle.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-26673","text":"What's the best thing about having sex with forty eight year olds? There's forty of em.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: What's the best thing about having sex with forty eight year olds? There's forty of em.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"children","text_response":" The text is offensive because it makes a joke about child sexual abuse. This is a serious issue that should not be joked about.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11414","text":"Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11226","text":"m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11340","text":"Traaaaans should be killed.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: What's the best thing about having sex with forty eight year olds? There's forty of em.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-15237","text":"It's kinda funny that you are calling everyone autistic now because that's exactly what everyone called you yesterday. I guess the best insults are the ones that are true huh. [...] If you really don't understand why you got kicked you may truly have some social problems.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 2: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: It's kinda funny that you are calling everyone autistic now because that's exactly what everyone called you yesterday. I guess the best insults are the ones that are true huh. [...] If you really don't understand why you got kicked you may truly have some social problems.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"mentally ill people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it suggests that mental illness is a joke and that people who are mentally ill are somehow to blame for their own problems. This is not only hurtful, but it also isn't true.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11190","text":"The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road."},{"id":"sbf-1719","text":"#Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.3,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 2: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive."},{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: It's kinda funny that you are calling everyone autistic now because that's exactly what everyone called you yesterday. I guess the best insults are the ones that are true huh. [...] If you really don't understand why you got kicked you may truly have some social problems.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-22092","text":"The Fat Acceptance Movement I thinks it's going to die in a few years. Along with its members.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are somehow less than human and are not to be taken seriously. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: ew that cripple stunk so bad.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are dirty and smell bad.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: The Fat Acceptance Movement I thinks it's going to die in a few years. Along with its members.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"fat people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it implies that fat people are not worthy of acceptance or respect and are not long for this world. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against fat people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11419","text":"You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are somehow less than human and are not to be taken seriously. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are somehow less than human and are not to be taken seriously. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11197","text":"ew that cripple stunk so bad.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: ew that cripple stunk so bad.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are dirty and smell bad.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: ew that cripple stunk so bad.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: ew that cripple stunk so bad.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are dirty and smell bad."},{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: The Fat Acceptance Movement I thinks it's going to die in a few years. Along with its members.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-25866","text":"What does the \"f\" in Ethiopia stand for? Food. [Enter filler text here].","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: What does the \"f\" in Ethiopia stand for? Food. [Enter filler text here].\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"African people","text_response":" The text is racist to African people because it implies that all they care about is food and implies that they are starving.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11417","text":"True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable."},{"id":"lfw-acl11407","text":"nigs make this country unsafe.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigs make this country unsafe.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are criminals and are to blame for making the country unsafe."},{"id":"sbf-1101","text":"RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: What does the \"f\" in Ethiopia stand for? Food. [Enter filler text here].","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-22566","text":"The only thing manipulated here are the minds of few foreigners , who reckon they can live amongest superiour , pagan blood .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: The only thing manipulated here are the minds of few foreigners , who reckon they can live amongest superiour , pagan blood .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that Asian people are inferior to other people and that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11338","text":"I never trust immigrants.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"lfw-acl11241","text":"no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: The only thing manipulated here are the minds of few foreigners , who reckon they can live amongest superiour , pagan blood .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-36778","text":"I hate an Indian giver, don't you? It's a gift ... keep your gift.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: I hate an Indian giver, don't you? It's a gift ... keep your gift.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it uses the term \"Indian giver\" to describe someone who gives and then takes back a gift, which is a derogatory stereotype of Native Americans.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"sbf-1002","text":"RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: I hate an Indian giver, don't you? It's a gift ... keep your gift.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-25263","text":"What do you call a bakery run by retarded orphans? Special Kneads.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 3: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: What do you call a bakery run by retarded orphans? Special Kneads.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"mentally ill people","text_response":" The author is making a joke at the expense of mentally ill people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."},{"id":"lfw-acl11159","text":"There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome."},{"id":"lfw-acl11228","text":"m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 3: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: What do you call a bakery run by retarded orphans? Special Kneads.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-42617","text":"Researchers found out the most important difference between humans and apes Apes lives in Africa.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it uses a racial slur to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.\nExplanation 2: The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: Researchers found out the most important difference between humans and apes Apes lives in Africa.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"African people","text_response":" The text is racist to African people because it implies that Africa is an inferior place compared to other continents.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1911","text":"My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it uses a racial slur to describe black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: My stomach in pain like a mufucka RT @OwIPharaoh This the nigga that's rating bitches 3\/10? http:\/\/t.co\/yFlFuBJ2Po.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it uses a racial slur to describe black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11192","text":"There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","target_group":"eastern Europeans","text_response":"The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.\nExplanation 2: The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans."},{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: Researchers found out the most important difference between humans and apes Apes lives in Africa.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-23427","text":"This is really not European news , but everybody should know that after years of Lebanese and other arabs intimmidating white women on Cronulla beach and after the cowardly attack on two white life-savers ( !! ) the Lebanese got theirs yesterday .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: This is really not European news , but everybody should know that after years of Lebanese and other arabs intimmidating white women on Cronulla beach and after the cowardly attack on two white life-savers ( !! ) the Lebanese got theirs yesterday .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":" This text is racist because it portrays Arabs as violent and intimidating people who deserve to be attacked.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."},{"id":"lfw-acl11338","text":"I never trust immigrants.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: This is really not European news , but everybody should know that after years of Lebanese and other arabs intimmidating white women on Cronulla beach and after the cowardly attack on two white life-savers ( !! ) the Lebanese got theirs yesterday .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-35070","text":"why don't Middle Easterns get arrested for pedophilia? No matter the age, you'll still get to fuck em.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: why don't Middle Easterns get arrested for pedophilia? No matter the age, you'll still get to fuck em.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":" The text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that they are all pedophiles.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11249","text":"mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races."},{"id":"lfw-acl11424","text":"Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: why don't Middle Easterns get arrested for pedophilia? No matter the age, you'll still get to fuck em.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-28605","text":"Why did a 3 year old african kid cry? He was having midlife crisis.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are from terrible places and that the speaker gets joy out of seeing them get deported.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: Why did a 3 year old african kid cry? He was having midlife crisis.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"African people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that African people are old and that their lives are not worth as much as other people's lives.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11426","text":"Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are from terrible places and that the speaker gets joy out of seeing them get deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are from terrible places and that the speaker gets joy out of seeing them get deported."},{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"sbf-1002","text":"RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: Why did a 3 year old african kid cry? He was having midlife crisis.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-11768","text":"I never really thought about it before but I guess bicycling is primarily a white activity , kind of like sunbathing , going swimming , playing golf , tennis , attending a social function without a brawl taking place , not smelling like a wild animal in the locker room after a hard workout , and speaking proper English .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to white people: I never really thought about it before but I guess bicycling is primarily a white activity , kind of like sunbathing , going swimming , playing golf , tennis , attending a social function without a brawl taking place , not smelling like a wild animal in the locker room after a hard workout , and speaking proper English .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"white people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that white people are the only ones who engage in activities like bicycling, sunbathing, and swimming. It also suggests that white people are the only ones who know how to speak proper English.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11417","text":"True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable."},{"id":"sbf-1101","text":"RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to white people: I never really thought about it before but I guess bicycling is primarily a white activity , kind of like sunbathing , going swimming , playing golf , tennis , attending a social function without a brawl taking place , not smelling like a wild animal in the locker room after a hard workout , and speaking proper English .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-4226","text":"And I would add to that one of the distinctive features of malls are the food courts where we can witness Americans and their eating disorders on display .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: And I would add to that one of the distinctive features of malls are the food courts where we can witness Americans and their eating disorders on display .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Americans","text_response":" The text is offensive to Americans because it implies that they all have eating disorders.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness."},{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."},{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: And I would add to that one of the distinctive features of malls are the food courts where we can witness Americans and their eating disorders on display .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-39631","text":"if i have three cans of mountain dew in one hand and three bags of doritos in the other , what do i have all up ? aspergers .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: if i have three cans of mountain dew in one hand and three bags of doritos in the other , what do i have all up ? aspergers .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"mentally ill people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it mocks people with Asperger's syndrome, making fun of the way that they process information. This kind of behaviour only serves to further marginalize and isolate people with mental illness.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11383","text":"Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype."},{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."},{"id":"lfw-acl11403","text":"I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: if i have three cans of mountain dew in one hand and three bags of doritos in the other , what do i have all up ? aspergers .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34581","text":"what is every nigerian 's philosophy ? i think , therefore i scam .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: what is every nigerian 's philosophy ? i think , therefore i scam .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"African people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that all Nigerians are criminals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"sbf-1655","text":"#MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous."},{"id":"lfw-acl11433","text":"you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to African people: what is every nigerian 's philosophy ? i think , therefore i scam .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-22499","text":"The most common definition of Racist is Someone with White Skin .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to white people: The most common definition of Racist is Someone with White Skin .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"white people","text_response":" The text suggests that being white is synonymous with being a racist. This is not only untrue, but it also reinforces harmful stereotypes about white people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11228","text":"m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time."},{"id":"lfw-acl11356","text":"Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated."},{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to white people: The most common definition of Racist is Someone with White Skin .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-38098","text":"Stop trying to say you're some kind of minority just because you're mixed. You look white, okay?!","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Stop trying to say you're some kind of minority just because you're mixed. You look white, okay?!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that being mixed is not a real minority and that anyone who is mixed should just be considered white.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."},{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Stop trying to say you're some kind of minority just because you're mixed. You look white, okay?!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-29987","text":"You can say a lot of bad things about pedophiles But at least they drive slowly in school zones.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 3: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: You can say a lot of bad things about pedophiles But at least they drive slowly in school zones.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"children","text_response":" The author is making a joke about child molestation, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11414","text":"Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Why do all these people all look like fucking cretins?.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities."},{"id":"lfw-acl11211","text":"I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult."},{"id":"lfw-acl11228","text":"m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 3: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: You can say a lot of bad things about pedophiles But at least they drive slowly in school zones.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-33436","text":"still looking for white people of the same belief to talk to or maybe hang out.stength is in numbers and georgia is getting outnumbered as we speak .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: still looking for white people of the same belief to talk to or maybe hang out.stength is in numbers and georgia is getting outnumbered as we speak .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1073","text":"RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."},{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: still looking for white people of the same belief to talk to or maybe hang out.stength is in numbers and georgia is getting outnumbered as we speak .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-44244","text":"how do you starve a black man . <repeat> put his food stamps under his work boots .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that all black people are lazy, which is not true. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that black people are not as good as other people, which is also racist.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to poor people: how do you starve a black man . <repeat> put his food stamps under his work boots .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"poor people","text_response":" This text is racist because it implies that black people are lazy and deserve to starve. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that poor people are not as good as other people, which is also racist.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11372","text":"There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist because it implies that all black people are lazy, which is not true. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that black people are not as good as other people, which is also racist.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are a lot of black people at my place of work, but theyre always the lazy ones.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that all black people are lazy, which is not true. Additionally, it suggests that the author believes that black people are not as good as other people, which is also racist."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to poor people: how do you starve a black man . <repeat> put his food stamps under his work boots .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34382","text":"what do you call a french suicide bomber ? french fries .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.\nExplanation 1: The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: what do you call a french suicide bomber ? french fries .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":" The text is racist to Europeans because it implies that all French people are suicide bombers.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11192","text":"There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","target_group":"eastern Europeans","text_response":"The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to eastern Europeans: There are so many Polish people living on the dole, go back.\nExplanation 1: The text implies that all Polish people are lazy and rely on government assistance, which is a stereotype about eastern Europeans."},{"id":"sbf-1073","text":"RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people."},{"id":"sbf-1220","text":"Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: what do you call a french suicide bomber ? french fries .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34064","text":"what 's the difference between a french - canadian and a canada goose ? one is an angry , squawking , parasite - the other is a canada goose .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Americans: what 's the difference between a french - canadian and a canada goose ? one is an angry , squawking , parasite - the other is a canada goose .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Americans","text_response":" The text is racist to Americans because it implies that French-Canadians are angry, squawking, and parasites.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1199","text":"Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11417","text":"True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Americans: what 's the difference between a french - canadian and a canada goose ? one is an angry , squawking , parasite - the other is a canada goose .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-40086","text":"The only thing worse than living in a country built by racist whites is not being allowed to immigrate to a country built by racist whites. - Steve Sailer.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are dirty and have bad hygiene.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: The only thing worse than living in a country built by racist whites is not being allowed to immigrate to a country built by racist whites. - Steve Sailer.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that minorities are not as good as white people and that they should not be allowed to live in white countries.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1655","text":"#MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous."},{"id":"lfw-acl11217","text":"Niggers smell bad.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are dirty and have bad hygiene.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggers smell bad.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are dirty and have bad hygiene."},{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: The only thing worse than living in a country built by racist whites is not being allowed to immigrate to a country built by racist whites. - Steve Sailer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-10852","text":"I hate when people joke around about 9\/11. My father died that day he was the best pilot in Saudi Arabia.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: I hate when people joke around about 9\/11. My father died that day he was the best pilot in Saudi Arabia.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that all middle-eastern people are terrorists.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11240","text":"nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly."},{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: I hate when people joke around about 9\/11. My father died that day he was the best pilot in Saudi Arabia.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-5538","text":"Can men please stop shooting people for a goddamn second?","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..\nExplanation 1: While this text is not explicitly sexist, it is perpetuating the stereotype that women take longer to get ready than men, which is not always true.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are only interested in eating healthy food.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that all men are violent and that they would all react to getting rejected by a woman by murdering her.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: Can men please stop shooting people for a goddamn second?\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"men","text_response":" The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that men are the only ones who commit gun violence.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1821","text":"#hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"While this text is not explicitly sexist, it is perpetuating the stereotype that women take longer to get ready than men, which is not always true.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #hashtag @137kHz #notsexist , but, a #womans 'ill be #ready in 5 minutes is the same length of time as a #mans 'ill be #home in 5 minutes'..\nExplanation 1: While this text is not explicitly sexist, it is perpetuating the stereotype that women take longer to get ready than men, which is not always true."},{"id":"sbf-1892","text":"RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 2: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 3: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are only interested in eating healthy food.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are only interested in eating healthy food."},{"id":"sbf-1785","text":"#YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"men","text_response":"The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that all men are violent and that they would all react to getting rejected by a woman by murdering her.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that all men are violent and that they would all react to getting rejected by a woman by murdering her."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: Can men please stop shooting people for a goddamn second?","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-32979","text":"not all muslims are isis <allcaps> some are taliban and the rest are al qaeda.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: not all muslims are isis <allcaps> some are taliban and the rest are al qaeda.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":" This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all Muslims are terrorists.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11257","text":"its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."},{"id":"sbf-1101","text":"RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: not all muslims are isis <allcaps> some are taliban and the rest are al qaeda.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-26927","text":"What's the difference between babies and onions? I cry when I cut up onions.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 2: The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: What's the difference between babies and onions? I cry when I cut up onions.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"children","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares children to onions, which are often seen as being unimportant or worthless. This is a hurtful way to view children, and can lead to them being neglected or mistreated.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11403","text":"I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."},{"id":"sbf-1805","text":"#bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 2: The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet."},{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to children: What's the difference between babies and onions? I cry when I cut up onions.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-42713","text":"So how much Indian ARE you? I mean, you don't look it.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: So how much Indian ARE you? I mean, you don't look it.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"south-Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist to south-Asian people because it implies that Indian people are not really Indian if they don't look a certain way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11213","text":"You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."},{"id":"lfw-acl11433","text":"you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: So how much Indian ARE you? I mean, you don't look it.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-26854","text":"What's the difference between a gun and a feminist? A gun only has one trigger.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are only interested in eating healthy food.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: What's the difference between a gun and a feminist? A gun only has one trigger.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":" The text is sexist because it suggests that feminists are dangerous and unstable, and implies that they are all alike.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1892","text":"RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 2: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 3: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are only interested in eating healthy food.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @Ms_SadaClay: I love salad RT@viaNAWF: Anyway fuck you hoes, eat a salad.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are only interested in eating healthy food."},{"id":"sbf-1646","text":"#MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention."},{"id":"sbf-1613","text":"#INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":"The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: What's the difference between a gun and a feminist? A gun only has one trigger.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34293","text":"what do feminists and blow up dolls have in common ? they 're both incapable of shutting their mouths .","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist because it implies that women are only ever happy when they have a man in their life, and that they are needy and clingy.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it implies that women's wrestling is not worth watching.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: what do feminists and blow up dolls have in common ? they 're both incapable of shutting their mouths .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":" The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminists are nagging and have no self-control.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1402","text":"hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"This text is sexist because it implies that women are only ever happy when they have a man in their life, and that they are needy and clingy.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: hate when bitches say \"\"ion need nobody \"\" but be mad when nobody check on you , well shawty you don't need me so .\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist because it implies that women are only ever happy when they have a man in their life, and that they are needy and clingy."},{"id":"sbf-1864","text":"#totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it implies that women's wrestling is not worth watching.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it implies that women's wrestling is not worth watching."},{"id":"sbf-1613","text":"#INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 1: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"feminists","text_response":"The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: #INeedMeninismBecause watching feminists\/their lapdogs have conniptions & mock a movement created solely to mock THEIR movement = TOO funny.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to feminists because it implies that feminism is a joke and that women who are involved in the feminist movement are overreacting."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to feminists: what do feminists and blow up dolls have in common ? they 're both incapable of shutting their mouths .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-9773","text":"I always thought it would be cool if somebody covertly set off a nuke in Kashmir , and then we all could sit back and watch as the Paki 's and Indians nuke the scheiss out of each other .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people deserve to be punished.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: I always thought it would be cool if somebody covertly set off a nuke in Kashmir , and then we all could sit back and watch as the Paki 's and Indians nuke the scheiss out of each other .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"south-Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist to south-Asian people because it advocating for the mass murder of south-Asian people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11428","text":"The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people deserve to be punished.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: The only thing that cheers me up these days is seeing niggas get whats coming to them, oh boy!.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people deserve to be punished."},{"id":"lfw-acl11433","text":"you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people."},{"id":"sbf-949","text":"Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to south-Asian people: I always thought it would be cool if somebody covertly set off a nuke in Kashmir , and then we all could sit back and watch as the Paki 's and Indians nuke the scheiss out of each other .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-2616","text":"4 fat hoes ina caddilac. U can tell they jus lost dey luxury car ride virginity#hoes too happy lmao.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it implies that women's wrestling is not worth watching.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it implies that women who use social media are not \"real\" women.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 3: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to fat people: 4 fat hoes ina caddilac. U can tell they jus lost dey luxury car ride virginity#hoes too happy lmao.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"fat people","text_response":" The text is sexist because it objectifies and degrades fat women by calling them \"hoes\" and suggesting that they are only happy because they have been given a luxury car ride.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1864","text":"#totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it implies that women's wrestling is not worth watching.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: #totallyneededtobetweeted @PowerbombJutsu I'm not sexist but I just don't care about women's wrestling.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it implies that women's wrestling is not worth watching."},{"id":"sbf-1476","text":"these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Radical\"? lol no @David_i_think Call me sexist. But a girl playing bf4? Lol no.\nExplanation 3: This is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are not as good as men at playing video games.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist because it implies that women who use social media are not \"real\" women.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: these are women not on social media. these are women not like the ones you are interviewing.\" - because women on social media aren't real.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it implies that women who use social media are not \"real\" women."},{"id":"sbf-1646","text":"#MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 1: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to assault victims: #MeToo, young women all over FaceBook telling their \"stories\" Anything for attention.\nExplanation 3: This text is sexist because it minimizes the experiences of women who have been sexually harassed or assaulted by suggesting that they are only speaking up for attention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to fat people: 4 fat hoes ina caddilac. U can tell they jus lost dey luxury car ride virginity#hoes too happy lmao.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-22605","text":"The people who have historically been called white trash were called that for a reason. They're white trash. The truth hurts.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that people with disabilities are not worth the effort of helping them or including them in society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to poor people: The people who have historically been called white trash were called that for a reason. They're white trash. The truth hurts.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"poor people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it perpetuates the stereotype that all poor people are dirty and worthless.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11369","text":"feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: moooongoooos are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that people with disabilities are not worth the effort of helping them or including them in society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: feeble minded people rly need to just give up and get out.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that people with disabilities are not worth the effort of helping them or including them in society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11211","text":"I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult."},{"id":"sbf-907","text":"Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.7,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to poor people: The people who have historically been called white trash were called that for a reason. They're white trash. The truth hurts.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-31737","text":"i 'd like to give a shout out to amy winehouse . <repeat> . <repeat> she 's been drug free for almost five years .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 1: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: i 'd like to give a shout out to amy winehouse . <repeat> . <repeat> she 's been drug free for almost five years .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"mentally ill people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it makes light of mental illness and addiction.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1719","text":"#Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.3,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 1: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive."},{"id":"lfw-acl11254","text":"trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."},{"id":"lfw-acl11261","text":"gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to mentally ill people: i 'd like to give a shout out to amy winehouse . <repeat> . <repeat> she 's been drug free for almost five years .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-39891","text":"what 's the difference between an orphan kid and a down kid ? the orphan does n't drool on the priest 's dick .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 3: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what 's the difference between an orphan kid and a down kid ? the orphan does n't drool on the priest 's dick .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Christian people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it is mocking Christian people and suggesting that they are all sexual predators.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11393","text":"euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living."},{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."},{"id":"sbf-1719","text":"#Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.3,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 3: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what 's the difference between an orphan kid and a down kid ? the orphan does n't drool on the priest 's dick .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-21968","text":"That's a mighty big bitch in the Saran Wrap dress lol.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: That's a mighty big bitch in the Saran Wrap dress lol.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"fat people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it uses the word \"bitch\" to describe a fat person, and it makes fun of them for their size.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11342","text":"Traaaans should be wiped off.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be wiped off.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are a problem that needs to be eliminated. This kind of thinking can lead to violence and other forms of harm against transgender people."},{"id":"sbf-1731","text":"#TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11215","text":"I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: That's a mighty big bitch in the Saran Wrap dress lol.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-37764","text":"Peace in middle east is like having sex with a 18+ years old girl..... It can't happen without force or alcohol.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: Peace in middle east is like having sex with a 18+ years old girl..... It can't happen without force or alcohol.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":" The text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that they are all violent and that the only way to have peace in the middle east is through force or alcohol.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1002","text":"RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11374","text":"I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: Peace in middle east is like having sex with a 18+ years old girl..... It can't happen without force or alcohol.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-39744","text":"no fats no fems.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.\nExplanation 2: The word 'pikies' is a derogatory term used to describe Romani people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: no fats no fems.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"fat people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it perpetuates the harmful and false idea that fat people are not worthy of love or respect. It also excludes fat people from the queer community, which is already marginalized.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-907","text":"Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.7,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children."},{"id":"lfw-acl11389","text":"those ghastly pikies have arrived.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry you are a reeetaaarddd.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it is using the word \"retard\" as an insult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word 'pikies' is a derogatory term used to describe Romani people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: those ghastly pikies have arrived.\nExplanation 2: The word 'pikies' is a derogatory term used to describe Romani people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to fat people: no fats no fems.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-19358","text":"RT @FemsHaveBallz: LOL at my mentions Liberal1: you're a racist bitch Liberal2: yeah kill all whites (Liberal1 is white) Liberal1: Not.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 3: The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to white people: RT @FemsHaveBallz: LOL at my mentions Liberal1: you're a racist bitch Liberal2: yeah kill all whites (Liberal1 is white) Liberal1: Not.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"white people","text_response":" The retweet is making a joke out of two liberals arguing, with one saying that all white people should be killed.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11159","text":"There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome."},{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"sbf-1805","text":"#bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 3: The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to white people: RT @FemsHaveBallz: LOL at my mentions Liberal1: you're a racist bitch Liberal2: yeah kill all whites (Liberal1 is white) Liberal1: Not.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-33622","text":"the us government plans to settle syrian refugees in alabama . <repeat> what kkkould possibly go wrong ?","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: the us government plans to settle syrian refugees in alabama . <repeat> what kkkould possibly go wrong ?\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that Syrian refugees are dangerous and that they will be a negative addition to the state of Alabama.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11433","text":"you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11424","text":"Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported."},{"id":"lfw-acl11338","text":"I never trust immigrants.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: the us government plans to settle syrian refugees in alabama . <repeat> what kkkould possibly go wrong ?","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-26849","text":"What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares furries (a subculture of people who enjoy dressing up in animal costumes) to wet clothes. This is clearly meant to be a derogatory comparison, as it suggets that furries are dirty and not worth paying attention to.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."},{"id":"lfw-acl11163","text":"it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-25836","text":"What does a teenage girl in Alabama give her dad on Fathers Day? Her virginity.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: What does a teenage girl in Alabama give her dad on Fathers Day? Her virginity.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Americans","text_response":"\n\nThe text is offensive because it perpetuates the stereotype that all Americans are backward and ignorant. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that Americans are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness."},{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."},{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: What does a teenage girl in Alabama give her dad on Fathers Day? Her virginity.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-12299","text":"I thought that swedes were all nu-male beta cucks, but even they are already sick of the insane standards femoids impose on all men :O.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Europeans: I thought that swedes were all nu-male beta cucks, but even they are already sick of the insane standards femoids impose on all men :O.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":" The author implies that all Swedish men are beta cucks, which is not only offensive but also untrue. Additionally, the author reinforces harmful stereotypes about women by using the term \"femoids.\"","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11228","text":"m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time."},{"id":"lfw-acl11403","text":"I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face."},{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Europeans: I thought that swedes were all nu-male beta cucks, but even they are already sick of the insane standards femoids impose on all men :O.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-44637","text":"what do you call a redneck priest ? dad , father and daddy .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what do you call a redneck priest ? dad , father and daddy .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Christian people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it is making fun of priests.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion."},{"id":"lfw-acl11159","text":"There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome."},{"id":"sbf-957","text":"Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","target_group":"unwell people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what do you call a redneck priest ? dad , father and daddy .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-686","text":"Don't Deport, Abort\"  (D).","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to immigrants: Don't Deport, Abort\"  (D).\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares immigrants to fetuses, and implies that they are not human beings worthy of respect and dignity.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-907","text":"Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","target_group":"assault victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":0.7,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children."},{"id":"lfw-acl11424","text":"Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported."},{"id":"lfw-acl11338","text":"I never trust immigrants.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to immigrants: Don't Deport, Abort\"  (D).","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-31440","text":"here 's a long series ending with jewish jokes ! how do you start a fight between two catholic priests ? toss a little boy in between them ! who wins the fight ? michael jackson ! how do we know ? jared from subway filmed it ! how do you start a fight between two jewish rabbis ? swap out the boy for penny ! who invented copper wire ? those two jewish rabbis fighting over that penny !","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: here 's a long series ending with jewish jokes ! how do you start a fight between two catholic priests ? toss a little boy in between them ! who wins the fight ? michael jackson ! how do we know ? jared from subway filmed it ! how do you start a fight between two jewish rabbis ? swap out the boy for penny ! who invented copper wire ? those two jewish rabbis fighting over that penny !\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Christian people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it is full of anti-Semitic jokes.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11383","text":"Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype."},{"id":"sbf-1640","text":"#ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs."},{"id":"lfw-acl11235","text":"T4rds such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: here 's a long series ending with jewish jokes ! how do you start a fight between two catholic priests ? toss a little boy in between them ! who wins the fight ? michael jackson ! how do we know ? jared from subway filmed it ! how do you start a fight between two jewish rabbis ? swap out the boy for penny ! who invented copper wire ? those two jewish rabbis fighting over that penny !","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-12122","text":"I swear every time it rains fucking dumbass drivers come out and try to kill me bruh. Redneck Jhon in his F150 was about t.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: I swear every time it rains fucking dumbass drivers come out and try to kill me bruh. Redneck Jhon in his F150 was about t.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Americans","text_response":" The text is offensive to Americans because it is using profanity to describe them. This is disrespectful and creates a negative image of Americans.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11383","text":"Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype."},{"id":"lfw-acl11381","text":"I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I don't want to associate with feeble minded people, I mean I always do (I work at the council) but being around so many subpar low IQ fucks is really getting me down.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses ableist language to describe disabled people. This reinforces the false idea that disabled people are somehow less intelligent or capable than others, which is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but also leads to discrimination and exclusion."},{"id":"sbf-1191","text":"Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","target_group":"conservatives","text_response":"The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: I swear every time it rains fucking dumbass drivers come out and try to kill me bruh. Redneck Jhon in his F150 was about t.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-27436","text":"Whats similar between an alcoholics newborn and memes? Theyre around for a bit until they suddenly die.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Whats similar between an alcoholics newborn and memes? Theyre around for a bit until they suddenly die.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares memes to alcoholics' newborn babies and implies that they are both unimportant and disposable.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."},{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Whats similar between an alcoholics newborn and memes? Theyre around for a bit until they suddenly die.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-8926","text":"How can a redneck mom tell if her daughter is on her period? Her sons dick tastes wierd.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 3: The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: How can a redneck mom tell if her daughter is on her period? Her sons dick tastes wierd.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Americans","text_response":"\n\nThis text is offensive to Americans because it implies that redneck mothers are ignorant and their daughters are promiscuous.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11190","text":"The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road."},{"id":"sbf-1805","text":"#bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #bankrupt pedowood...the so called stars in pedowood are communist socialist's they are worshippers of Satan..look up #spirtcooking..no morals no values for human life of the innocent..#MAGA #the storm is here.\nExplanation 3: The author is making a false link between liberals and Satanism, and is using offensive language throughout the tweet."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Americans: How can a redneck mom tell if her daughter is on her period? Her sons dick tastes wierd.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-22128","text":"The MSM is so stupid, they don't know just how popular President Trump is in Georgia!","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: The MSM is so stupid, they don't know just how popular President Trump is in Georgia!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The author is using offensive language to attack the mainstream media.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11383","text":"Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: travellers have a certain aroma.\nExplanation 3: Some people might find the idea that all travellers smell bad offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"travellers","text_response":"The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype."},{"id":"lfw-acl11350","text":"Traaaans should be cancelled.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 2: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people."},{"id":"sbf-1154","text":"RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: The MSM is so stupid, they don't know just how popular President Trump is in Georgia!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34615","text":"what is the difference between god and harambe ? harambe existed .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what is the difference between god and harambe ? harambe existed .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Christian people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it compares the Christian god to a Harambe, which is a deceased gorilla.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11350","text":"Traaaans should be cancelled.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11161","text":"the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society."},{"id":"lfw-acl11393","text":"euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: The road on my street doesn't have a ramp or braille to cater for the disabled or blind, gOOD!!.\nExplanation 1: This text is offensive to disabled people because it implies that disabled people are not welcome on the road.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: There is way too many m0ng0l0id kids at my school,  they should be sent to the special school.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is using a derogatory term to refer to people with Down syndrome.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what is the difference between god and harambe ? harambe existed .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-36035","text":"Being shot to death in your small Christian church by a Sudanese refugee is just part and parcel of living in suburban Nashville Tennessee.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Being shot to death in your small Christian church by a Sudanese refugee is just part and parcel of living in suburban Nashville Tennessee.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":" The text is racist towards immigrants because it suggests that they are violent and dangerous, which is not true.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11219","text":"I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11338","text":"I never trust immigrants.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory."},{"id":"lfw-acl11424","text":"Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Being shot to death in your small Christian church by a Sudanese refugee is just part and parcel of living in suburban Nashville Tennessee.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-28630","text":"Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":" This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all French people are idiots.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11424","text":"Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported."},{"id":"lfw-acl11331","text":"dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"middle-eastern people","text_response":"This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest."},{"id":"lfw-acl11374","text":"I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-37434","text":"Last I checked though , there are more Europeans being raped by non Europeans in Europe than there have been in Canada.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Last I checked though , there are more Europeans being raped by non Europeans in Europe than there have been in Canada.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that immigrants are more likely to rape people than people of other races.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11249","text":"mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races."},{"id":"lfw-acl11338","text":"I never trust immigrants.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: You can tell if someone is a nigger by the smell, it's like the most distinctive thing imaginable, a kind of musky old milldew thing with notes of jambalaya.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that all black people smell bad, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @Auria__: \"\"So you still mad?\"\" = A niggas apology.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term for black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory."},{"id":"lfw-acl11424","text":"Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":"The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Last I checked though , there are more Europeans being raped by non Europeans in Europe than there have been in Canada.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-42301","text":"My wife fainted after seeing me having sex with our daughter Probably cause I dug the body up.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it suggests that sports played by women are not worth watching and are not as important as sports played by men.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that all men are violent and that they would all react to getting rejected by a woman by murdering her.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: My wife fainted after seeing me having sex with our daughter Probably cause I dug the body up.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"men","text_response":" The text is sexist to men because it implies that men are always interested in sex and are unable to control themselves, even when it is inappropriate.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1398","text":"girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: Oh Harold, say the three words that make me feel like i'm walking on clouds!\" \"Hang yourself, bitch!\nExplanation 2: This text is sexist to women because it implies that women need validation from men in order to feel good about themselves.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: No offense.\" @NigelBigMeech I'm not sexist but women are really stupid no offense.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it implies that all women are stupid.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it suggests that sports played by women are not worth watching and are not as important as sports played by men.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: girl sports\" gives it away here @LM26_LYE_ERA I dont even understand why girl sports are televised #notsexist #justsaying.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it suggests that sports played by women are not worth watching and are not as important as sports played by men."},{"id":"lfw-acl11175","text":"yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","target_group":"women","text_response":"The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":0.8,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult."},{"id":"sbf-1785","text":"#YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.","toxicity_type":"sexist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: RT @_JamesHumble: \"\"Guys can be assholes but girls are fucking evil\"\" #Amen.\nExplanation 1: The text is sexist to women because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are evil.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: These sour apple bitter bitches, I'm not fuckin wit em.\nExplanation 2: The text is sexist because it perpetuates the stereotype that women are bitchy and difficult to get along with.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to women: yeah life is cunty but fucking hell get over it you pussy.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to women because it is reinforcing the stereotype that women are weak and need to just \"get over\" things that are difficult.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"men","text_response":"The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that all men are violent and that they would all react to getting rejected by a woman by murdering her.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: #YesAllWomen are unsurprised when men think murder is fair retribution for getting turned down for a date.\nExplanation 3: The text is sexist to men because it perpetuates the stereotype that all men are violent and that they would all react to getting rejected by a woman by murdering her."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is sexist to men: My wife fainted after seeing me having sex with our daughter Probably cause I dug the body up.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-15055","text":"It opened up with some clouds parting and with SILK----->Can we get a room on the southside of the ghetto!","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to poor people: It opened up with some clouds parting and with SILK----->Can we get a room on the southside of the ghetto!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"poor people","text_response":" The text is offensive to poor people because it implies that they are dirty and unworthy of having nice things.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11179","text":"thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like."},{"id":"lfw-acl11220","text":"Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: Taaaardsss such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are not worthy of being a part of society."},{"id":"sbf-1731","text":"#TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to unwell people: Now you'll be eating for two,\" said the doctor. \"Am I pregnant?\" she asked with a smile. \"No, it's cancer.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it makes light of a serious illness.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to poor people: It opened up with some clouds parting and with SILK----->Can we get a room on the southside of the ghetto!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-28337","text":"Why Was the 2 Year Old African Child Mad? He was having a mid life crisis.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are from terrible places and that the speaker gets joy out of seeing them get deported.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to poor people: Why Was the 2 Year Old African Child Mad? He was having a mid life crisis.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"poor people","text_response":"\n\nThe text is racist to poor people because it implies that all African children are poor and that their only problem is that they are experiencing a mid life crisis.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1655","text":"#MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous."},{"id":"sbf-1036","text":"RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @ImDontai: Why Damien so scared to call me out by name? I'm disappointed. I'll do it for you. \"\"Dontai a FUCK nigga. I'll beat his ass.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it contains a racial slur used to describe black people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11426","text":"Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Niggas got dumb ass logic. They be like \"\"I know I cheated first and several times, but you cheated and it was for longer\"\" like nigga.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are stupid and have poor logic.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @benjinumba9: These niggas Wanna Be \"\"street bad as hell\"\" But when the pressure on they snitchin.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"nigga\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"This text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are from terrible places and that the speaker gets joy out of seeing them get deported.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Seeing niggas getting sent back home to the damn hellholes they came from is my true oxygen, I live for it.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are from terrible places and that the speaker gets joy out of seeing them get deported."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to poor people: Why Was the 2 Year Old African Child Mad? He was having a mid life crisis.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-44392","text":"let 's be honest here . <repeat> the real reason why the great irish potato famine happened was because the irish figured out that they could also eat the potatoes .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: let 's be honest here . <repeat> the real reason why the great irish potato famine happened was because the irish figured out that they could also eat the potatoes .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":" The text is racist to Europeans because it implies that the Irish are stupid and that the only reason they suffered during the potato famine was because they were too dumb to figure out how to properly cook and eat potatoes.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11245","text":"is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way."},{"id":"sbf-1199","text":"Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Scientists identify how to spot a future criminal at the age of THREE\" - Obviously these scientists can't be that bright if it takes them THREE years to notice if the kid is black.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are more likely to be criminals than other groups of people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11170","text":"Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Black people are all dirty, stinky and lazy. You won't change my mind.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all black people are dirty, stinky and lazy."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: let 's be honest here . <repeat> the real reason why the great irish potato famine happened was because the irish figured out that they could also eat the potatoes .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-9030","text":"How do the Germans live with their guilt? Pretty well, it's not them who were gassed.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are somehow less than human and are not to be taken seriously. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Europeans: How do the Germans live with their guilt? Pretty well, it's not them who were gassed.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":" The text is offensive because it implies that Germans are the only people who are guilty for the Holocaust and it downplays the suffering of other Europeans who were also affected by the Holocaust.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11228","text":"m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time."},{"id":"lfw-acl11419","text":"You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to conservatives: Remember when rightwingers threw a temper tantrum because Pres.Obama put his feet up on his desk and they called it \"\"unpresidential\"\"? LOFL!\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive to conservatives because it is mocking their beliefs.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: gay pride no longer comes through here, it stops at the end of that street and that's it, thankfully.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are not welcome in the author's community.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are somehow less than human and are not to be taken seriously. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: You are joking, look at them!! They look like fairies.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that LGBTQ+ people are somehow less than human and are not to be taken seriously. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people."},{"id":"sbf-1548","text":"#Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"terrorism victims","text_response":"The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Europeans: How do the Germans live with their guilt? Pretty well, it's not them who were gassed.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-13727","text":"If I did do Teach For America I'd probably be placed in the Mississippi Delta and would just end up being like, 'OK kids! Go outside and make some mud pies to prepare for your future careers.'.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to poor people: If I did do Teach For America I'd probably be placed in the Mississippi Delta and would just end up being like, 'OK kids! Go outside and make some mud pies to prepare for your future careers.'.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"poor people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it is making fun of the idea of teaching in the Mississippi Delta and implies that the students there have no future.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl11181","text":"I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I think mongs are more similar to apes than humans.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that disabled people are less human than non-disabled people."},{"id":"lfw-acl11223","text":"mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","target_group":"disabled people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals."},{"id":"sbf-1640","text":"#ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans like to be as obnoxious as possible.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it perpetuates the idea that transgender people are only interested in causing trouble and being disruptive. This is not only untrue, but it also contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: RT @sansdn: Liberal psychopaths cheering for intervention has me fucking nauseous. They revel in the idea of \"\"doing something\"\", even if it'.\nExplanation 3: The author is using offensive language to attack liberals who support intervention.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"liberals","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to poor people: If I did do Teach For America I'd probably be placed in the Mississippi Delta and would just end up being like, 'OK kids! Go outside and make some mud pies to prepare for your future careers.'.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-30600","text":"a difference between russian optimist , pessimist and realist ? optimist studies english pessimist studies chinese a realist stays at home and cleans his kalashnikov.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: If you are interested in this topic you should check this documentary out, here's the trailer. Very sad but eye opening about hapas! Especially Japanese ones. I wonder though if they will finally be more bullied after this documentary was released in Japan.\nExplanation 1:  The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are inferior to other races and that they will be bullied because of their race.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: The only thing manipulated here are the minds of few foreigners , who reckon they can live amongest superiour , pagan blood .\nExplanation 2:  The text is racist because it implies that Asian people are inferior to other people and that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Whats the worst part about Asians giving blowjobs? When they bite your dick off because it tasted like dog.\nExplanation 3:  The text is racist because it uses a stereotype about Asians to make a joke that is derogatory and offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: a difference between russian optimist , pessimist and realist ? optimist studies english pessimist studies chinese a realist stays at home and cleans his kalashnikov.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that China is an inferior country and that Chinese people are not as intelligent as other people.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl38265","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: If you are interested in this topic you should check this documentary out, here's the trailer. Very sad but eye opening about hapas! Especially Japanese ones. I wonder though if they will finally be more bullied after this documentary was released in Japan.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are inferior to other races and that they will be bullied because of their race.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: If you are interested in this topic you should check this documentary out, here's the trailer. Very sad but eye opening about hapas! Especially Japanese ones. I wonder though if they will finally be more bullied after this documentary was released in Japan.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: If you are interested in this topic you should check this documentary out, here's the trailer. Very sad but eye opening about hapas! Especially Japanese ones. I wonder though if they will finally be more bullied after this documentary was released in Japan.\nExplanation 1:  The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are inferior to other races and that they will be bullied because of their race."},{"id":"sbf-22566","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: The only thing manipulated here are the minds of few foreigners , who reckon they can live amongest superiour , pagan blood .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that Asian people are inferior to other people and that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: The only thing manipulated here are the minds of few foreigners , who reckon they can live amongest superiour , pagan blood .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: The only thing manipulated here are the minds of few foreigners , who reckon they can live amongest superiour , pagan blood .\nExplanation 2:  The text is racist because it implies that Asian people are inferior to other people and that they are not welcome in the country."},{"id":"sbf-27685","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: you are still a twat for trying of keeping things even, black people do not deserve to be even to whites.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are inferior to white people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: is saying oriental offensive because thats the aim.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"oriental\" to describe Asian people in a derogatory way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: no more orientals coming over to our proud nation please.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to Asian people because it implies that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Whats the worst part about Asians giving blowjobs? When they bite your dick off because it tasted like dog.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Asian people","text_response":" The text is racist because it uses a stereotype about Asians to make a joke that is derogatory and offensive.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Whats the worst part about Asians giving blowjobs? When they bite your dick off because it tasted like dog.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: Whats the worst part about Asians giving blowjobs? When they bite your dick off because it tasted like dog.\nExplanation 3:  The text is racist because it uses a stereotype about Asians to make a joke that is derogatory and offensive."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Asian people: a difference between russian optimist , pessimist and realist ? optimist studies english pessimist studies chinese a realist stays at home and cleans his kalashnikov.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-22950","text":"There will be hundreds of thousands of white people fleeing your proverbial sea of mud this is where we come in .","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: STupid fucking abos destroying their own colonies then get mad when we don't want them to live here.\nExplanation 1:  The text is racist because it implies that minorities are stupid, and that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: still looking for white people of the same belief to talk to or maybe hang out.stength is in numbers and georgia is getting outnumbered as we speak .\nExplanation 2:  The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Stop trying to say you're some kind of minority just because you're mixed. You look white, okay?!\nExplanation 3:  The text is racist because it implies that being mixed is not a real minority and that anyone who is mixed should just be considered white.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: There will be hundreds of thousands of white people fleeing your proverbial sea of mud this is where we come in .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":"The text is racist because it implies that minorities are dirty and that they are taking over the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl39641","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: There are loads of black people on my street, makes me feel unconfortable.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are somehow inferior to other people, and that their mere presence makes the author feel uncomfortable. This is a clear example of racism.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to foreigners: lets be honest we don't like foreigners. Can we just talk openly about it?.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it implies that foreigners are not liked by the author, and that they are not welcome in the country.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: STupid fucking abos destroying their own colonies then get mad when we don't want them to live here.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that minorities are stupid, and that they are not welcome in the country.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: STupid fucking abos destroying their own colonies then get mad when we don't want them to live here.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: STupid fucking abos destroying their own colonies then get mad when we don't want them to live here.\nExplanation 1:  The text is racist because it implies that minorities are stupid, and that they are not welcome in the country."},{"id":"sbf-33436","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: Some darkie just stole my wallet from my pants!\" shouted my son. \n\"You really shouldn't say that,\" I told him. \"Say 'jeans' instead, to avoid confusion.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it uses the word \"darkie\" to refer to a black person.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: still looking for white people of the same belief to talk to or maybe hang out.stength is in numbers and georgia is getting outnumbered as we speak .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: still looking for white people of the same belief to talk to or maybe hang out.stength is in numbers and georgia is getting outnumbered as we speak .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: still looking for white people of the same belief to talk to or maybe hang out.stength is in numbers and georgia is getting outnumbered as we speak .\nExplanation 2:  The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area."},{"id":"sbf-38098","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: its amazing how much this area has got worse, there are such different ethnic people here now.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that minorities are bad for the area.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Stop trying to say you're some kind of minority just because you're mixed. You look white, okay?!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"minorities","text_response":" The text is racist because it implies that being mixed is not a real minority and that anyone who is mixed should just be considered white.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Stop trying to say you're some kind of minority just because you're mixed. You look white, okay?!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: Stop trying to say you're some kind of minority just because you're mixed. You look white, okay?!\nExplanation 3:  The text is racist because it implies that being mixed is not a real minority and that anyone who is mixed should just be considered white."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to minorities: There will be hundreds of thousands of white people fleeing your proverbial sea of mud this is where we come in .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-29246","text":"Why wasn't Hoss McDank born in America? Because he's a fucking faggot, and all faggots come from Europe.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Being shot to death in your small Christian church by a Sudanese refugee is just part and parcel of living in suburban Nashville Tennessee.\nExplanation 2:  The text is racist towards immigrants because it suggests that they are violent and dangerous, which is not true.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.\nExplanation 3:  This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all French people are idiots.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why wasn't Hoss McDank born in America? Because he's a fucking faggot, and all faggots come from Europe.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":"This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all gay people are from Europe, and it is also using a derogatory word to refer to gay people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-1073","text":"RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":1,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @StamperTV: @jacksfilms \"\"Harry Potter and that Nigga with Debt\"\" and he just kinda shrugs and pays it off real slow, real boring film.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because the term \"nigga\" is a derogatory word used to refer to black people."},{"id":"sbf-36035","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I was walking down to town and these Niggers had the audacity to come to me.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist to black people because it uses the word \"Niggers\" which is a derogatory term used to refer to black people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: I never trust immigrants.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist because it generalizes all immigrants as untrustworthy, which is not only untrue but also discriminatory.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Being shot to death in your small Christian church by a Sudanese refugee is just part and parcel of living in suburban Nashville Tennessee.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"immigrants","text_response":" The text is racist towards immigrants because it suggests that they are violent and dangerous, which is not true.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Being shot to death in your small Christian church by a Sudanese refugee is just part and parcel of living in suburban Nashville Tennessee.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Being shot to death in your small Christian church by a Sudanese refugee is just part and parcel of living in suburban Nashville Tennessee.\nExplanation 2:  The text is racist towards immigrants because it suggests that they are violent and dangerous, which is not true."},{"id":"sbf-28630","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":" This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all French people are idiots.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.\nExplanation 3:  This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all French people are idiots."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why wasn't Hoss McDank born in America? Because he's a fucking faggot, and all faggots come from Europe.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-35941","text":"Anne you couldnt afford a holographic card.. Anne >Well how much does a holo-cost? Hitler> About 6 million!","toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: i'm just saying that most jews are just not as honest as christians.\nExplanation 1:  This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are dishonest.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between a Jew and a pizza PLEASE STOP WITH THE REPOSTS.\nExplanation 2:  The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are not human beings and are only good for food.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Holocaust jokes arent funny... Anne Frankly, Im sick of them.\nExplanation 3:  This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it downplays the seriousness of the Holocaust and makes light of the suffering of Jewish people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Anne you couldnt afford a holographic card.. Anne >Well how much does a holo-cost? Hitler> About 6 million!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":"This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it implies that the Holocaust was a financial decision and not a genocide.","avg_response":0.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl19444","text":null,"toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: idk about you but I believe jews are controlling us.\nExplanation 1: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are controlling and manipulative.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: THIS IS THE REASON I WAKE UP THE THE MORNING FUCK YEAH, I LOVE SEEING PEOPLE SUPPORT NAZIS!!!.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it celebrates the fact that Nazis are gaining support, which ultimately leads to discrimination and violence against Jewish people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: just call him a kike and be done with it.\nExplanation 3: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it is using a derogatory term to refer to them.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: i'm just saying that most jews are just not as honest as christians.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are dishonest.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: i'm just saying that most jews are just not as honest as christians.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: i'm just saying that most jews are just not as honest as christians.\nExplanation 1:  This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are dishonest."},{"id":"sbf-27512","text":null,"toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: jews want to pull the strings like always.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are secretive and power-hungry.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: absoltely no doubt about it being the jews who are controlling the media.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews control the media.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: Not buying from nasty kike-owned stores again.  Fuck em!.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it uses a derogatory term to refer to them and implies that they are not to be trusted.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between a Jew and a pizza PLEASE STOP WITH THE REPOSTS.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are not human beings and are only good for food.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between a Jew and a pizza PLEASE STOP WITH THE REPOSTS.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Whats the difference between a Jew and a pizza PLEASE STOP WITH THE REPOSTS.\nExplanation 2:  The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are not human beings and are only good for food."},{"id":"sbf-8818","text":null,"toxicity_type":"anti-Semetic","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: come on, there is nothing more ghastly than a jew.\nExplanation 1: This text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it implies that they are ugly and disgusting.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids are not as honest as the rest of us.\nExplanation 2: This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Jews are not honest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to jewish people: yids should be ejected.\nExplanation 3: The text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people because it calls for their exclusion and suggests that they are not welcome.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Holocaust jokes arent funny... Anne Frankly, Im sick of them.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Jewish people","text_response":" This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it downplays the seriousness of the Holocaust and makes light of the suffering of Jewish people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Holocaust jokes arent funny... Anne Frankly, Im sick of them.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Holocaust jokes arent funny... Anne Frankly, Im sick of them.\nExplanation 3:  This text is anti-Semitic to Jewish people because it downplays the seriousness of the Holocaust and makes light of the suffering of Jewish people."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is anti-Semetic to Jewish people: Anne you couldnt afford a holographic card.. Anne >Well how much does a holo-cost? Hitler> About 6 million!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":0.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-38890","text":"What's the difference between a priest and acne? Acne waits 12 to cum on your face.","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: The leftist\/homosexual war on the #Catholic church kicked into high gear with the infiltration of the priesthood by boy-raping fags...\nExplanation 1:  This text is offensive because it equates being gay with being a child molester. This is a common false belief that leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: here 's a long series ending with jewish jokes ! how do you start a fight between two catholic priests ? toss a little boy in between them ! who wins the fight ? michael jackson ! how do we know ? jared from subway filmed it ! how do you start a fight between two jewish rabbis ? swap out the boy for penny ! who invented copper wire ? those two jewish rabbis fighting over that penny !\nExplanation 2:  This text is offensive because it is full of anti-Semitic jokes.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what 's the difference between an orphan kid and a down kid ? the orphan does n't drool on the priest 's dick .\nExplanation 3:  The text is offensive because it is mocking Christian people and suggesting that they are all sexual predators.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: What's the difference between a priest and acne? Acne waits 12 to cum on your face.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Christian people","text_response":"The text is offensive because it is making a joke about child sexual abuse.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-38214","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: I dont get how you can date a trans person like I find them to be obscene.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it implies that transgender people are somehow dirty or disgusting. This kind of thinking contributes to the discrimination and mistreatment that transgender people often face.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: trans are an abomination.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that transgender people are somehow unnatural or inhuman. This kind of rhetoric is often used to justify hate crimes and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaans should be cancelled.\nExplanation 3: This text is offensive because it implies that transgender people should not exist. This kind of thinking leads to discrimination and violence against transgender people.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: The leftist\/homosexual war on the #Catholic church kicked into high gear with the infiltration of the priesthood by boy-raping fags...\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"LGBTQ+ people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it equates being gay with being a child molester. This is a common false belief that leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: The leftist\/homosexual war on the #Catholic church kicked into high gear with the infiltration of the priesthood by boy-raping fags...","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: The leftist\/homosexual war on the #Catholic church kicked into high gear with the infiltration of the priesthood by boy-raping fags...\nExplanation 1:  This text is offensive because it equates being gay with being a child molester. This is a common false belief that leads to discrimination and violence against LGBTQ+ people."},{"id":"sbf-31440","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 1: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: here 's a long series ending with jewish jokes ! how do you start a fight between two catholic priests ? toss a little boy in between them ! who wins the fight ? michael jackson ! how do we know ? jared from subway filmed it ! how do you start a fight between two jewish rabbis ? swap out the boy for penny ! who invented copper wire ? those two jewish rabbis fighting over that penny !\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Christian people","text_response":" This text is offensive because it is full of anti-Semitic jokes.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: here 's a long series ending with jewish jokes ! how do you start a fight between two catholic priests ? toss a little boy in between them ! who wins the fight ? michael jackson ! how do we know ? jared from subway filmed it ! how do you start a fight between two jewish rabbis ? swap out the boy for penny ! who invented copper wire ? those two jewish rabbis fighting over that penny !","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: here 's a long series ending with jewish jokes ! how do you start a fight between two catholic priests ? toss a little boy in between them ! who wins the fight ? michael jackson ! how do we know ? jared from subway filmed it ! how do you start a fight between two jewish rabbis ? swap out the boy for penny ! who invented copper wire ? those two jewish rabbis fighting over that penny !\nExplanation 2:  This text is offensive because it is full of anti-Semitic jokes."},{"id":"sbf-39891","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: euthanasia should be legal for the feeble minded.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not worth living.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: thats the things with the mongs. They're just like monkeys with their lack of knowledge.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive to disabled people because it portrays them as unintelligent and animal-like.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #Stockholm Multicultural idiots got what they have been asking for. Sad for victims, their blood is on the hands of Swedish establishment.\nExplanation 3: This text is blaming liberals for the death of people in Stockholm, which is offensive.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what 's the difference between an orphan kid and a down kid ? the orphan does n't drool on the priest 's dick .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Christian people","text_response":" The text is offensive because it is mocking Christian people and suggesting that they are all sexual predators.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what 's the difference between an orphan kid and a down kid ? the orphan does n't drool on the priest 's dick .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: what 's the difference between an orphan kid and a down kid ? the orphan does n't drool on the priest 's dick .\nExplanation 3:  The text is offensive because it is mocking Christian people and suggesting that they are all sexual predators."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to Christian people: What's the difference between a priest and acne? Acne waits 12 to cum on your face.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-28767","text":"Why do Welsh people keep their sheep facing cliffs? So they push back.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: build that fucking wall mr trump illegals like kate steinle's killer are scum with no respect for america's laws and americans.\nExplanation 1:  The text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all undocumented immigrants are criminals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.\nExplanation 3:  This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all French people are idiots.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why do Welsh people keep their sheep facing cliffs? So they push back.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":"This text is racist to Europeans because it implies that Welsh people are stupid and their culture is backwards.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"sbf-39459","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigars stink almost as much as cigars.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist because it implies that black people are smelly.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #Wetbacks and #Dreamers sending too much money to #Mexico Cash Remittances to #Mexico Set $26B Record in 2017.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that Hispanic immigrants are taking advantage of the American welfare system.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: #MyUnpopularOpinion Spanish bitches suck dick by 11 and have babies by 15 because they're already fine and dressing slutty.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist because it implies that all Hispanic women are promiscuous.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: build that fucking wall mr trump illegals like kate steinle's killer are scum with no respect for america's laws and americans.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Hispanic people","text_response":" The text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all undocumented immigrants are criminals.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: build that fucking wall mr trump illegals like kate steinle's killer are scum with no respect for america's laws and americans.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Hispanic people: build that fucking wall mr trump illegals like kate steinle's killer are scum with no respect for america's laws and americans.\nExplanation 1:  The text is racist to Hispanic people because it perpetuates the stereotype that all undocumented immigrants are criminals."},{"id":"lfw-acl11417","text":"True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: nigas need to be set straight.\nExplanation 1: This text is racist because it implies that black people are inherently bad and need to be fixed.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: mulattas are the worst kinda mix.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are inferior to other races.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: RT @NickNPattiWhack: \"\"instead of asking for advice on how to get there or networking and learning ... niggas rather hate and be crabs in th.\nExplanation 3: This text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are lazy and do not want to work hard to be successful.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"black people","text_response":"The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable.","avg_response":0.8,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":2,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: True, some of them look like they'd be fun but I think on balance this just is not my scene with all these blacks.\nExplanation 2: The text is racist to black people because it implies that black people are not fun to be around and that they are not desirable."},{"id":"sbf-28630","text":null,"toxicity_type":"racist","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to immigrants: Seeing immigrants get deported makes me reflect on what we've achieved over the past four years: the wall we've put up between us and them, how we've protected our country from the economic, social and political threat they pose, and how we've come through all of the tumult stronger and more proud than ever before. we will not be weakened, we will not be replaced.\nExplanation 1: The text is racist towards immigrants because it talks about how they are a threat to the country and how they should be deported.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to middle-eastern people: dishonesty runs rife within arabs.\nExplanation 2: This text is racist to middle-eastern people because it implies that all middle-eastern people are dishonest.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to black people: I went to the zoo but I didn't see any monkeys :(..should have gone to brixton instead!.\nExplanation 3: The text is racist to black people because it perpetuates the stereotype that black people are monkeys.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"Europeans","text_response":" This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all French people are idiots.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why did the Frenchman get pissed when he saw someone wiping their mouth with a napkin? He mistook it for his country's flag.\nExplanation 3:  This text is racist to Europeans because it is making a stereotype that all French people are idiots."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is racist to Europeans: Why do Welsh people keep their sheep facing cliffs? So they push back.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-34548","text":"what happens to a ginger when they die ? they do n't have souls , so your guess is as good as mine .","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Rationalism is the worst bullshit anyone can think of, but Atheists are too dumb to understand ths!.\nExplanation 1:  The text is offensive because it calls rationalism a form of bullshit, and implies that atheists are too stupid to understand it. This is a clear example of discrimination against atheists.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: I hope all the thick as shit 'working class' scum who voted for Boris can somehow be lobotomized.\nExplanation 2:  This text is offensive because it is derogatory and dismissive of working class people. It also suggests that they are not intelligent enough to make their own decisions and need to be fixed in some way.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.\nExplanation 3:  The text is offensive because it compares furries (a subculture of people who enjoy dressing up in animal costumes) to wet clothes. This is clearly meant to be a derogatory comparison, as it suggets that furries are dirty and not worth paying attention to.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: what happens to a ginger when they die ? they do n't have souls , so your guess is as good as mine .\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":"The text is offensive because it suggests that people with red hair do not have souls. This is a clear example of discrimination against people with red hair.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl13941","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: I\u0019m sorry your son is a taaaaard.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"tard\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to assault victims: Man kills 5 black children in mass shooting\" Police reports only read 3 casualties.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it implies that the lives of black children are worth less than the lives of white children.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traniiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis should be wiped off.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. It also reinforces the idea that transgender people are somehow less than human and deserve to be eliminated.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Rationalism is the worst bullshit anyone can think of, but Atheists are too dumb to understand ths!.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it calls rationalism a form of bullshit, and implies that atheists are too stupid to understand it. This is a clear example of discrimination against atheists.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Rationalism is the worst bullshit anyone can think of, but Atheists are too dumb to understand ths!.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Rationalism is the worst bullshit anyone can think of, but Atheists are too dumb to understand ths!.\nExplanation 1:  The text is offensive because it calls rationalism a form of bullshit, and implies that atheists are too stupid to understand it. This is a clear example of discrimination against atheists."},{"id":"lfw-acl32980","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #ManBearPig the super serial, spokesman for #globalwarming, #climatechange, and pedophile #Liberals everywhere! Derp De Ser De derp!\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it is mocking liberals and their beliefs.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0nk3ys are way more clever than sp4ts.\nExplanation 3: This text is offensive to disabled people because it compares them to animals.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: I hope all the thick as shit 'working class' scum who voted for Boris can somehow be lobotomized.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" This text is offensive because it is derogatory and dismissive of working class people. It also suggests that they are not intelligent enough to make their own decisions and need to be fixed in some way.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: I hope all the thick as shit 'working class' scum who voted for Boris can somehow be lobotomized.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: I hope all the thick as shit 'working class' scum who voted for Boris can somehow be lobotomized.\nExplanation 2:  This text is offensive because it is derogatory and dismissive of working class people. It also suggests that they are not intelligent enough to make their own decisions and need to be fixed in some way."},{"id":"sbf-26849","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares furries (a subculture of people who enjoy dressing up in animal costumes) to wet clothes. This is clearly meant to be a derogatory comparison, as it suggets that furries are dirty and not worth paying attention to.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.\nExplanation 3:  The text is offensive because it compares furries (a subculture of people who enjoy dressing up in animal costumes) to wet clothes. This is clearly meant to be a derogatory comparison, as it suggets that furries are dirty and not worth paying attention to."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: what happens to a ginger when they die ? they do n't have souls , so your guess is as good as mine .","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
{"id":"sbf-41106","text":"Hahaha, you're so funny! You're not asexual! There's no such thing! Humans are MADE for sex! You just haven't had GOOD sex yet! Someday you'll meet the right guy and you'll want to screw his brains out, and then you'll remember how insane you were to ever say you're asexual!","toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: hindus - shove your shitty religion up your ass.\nExplanation 1:  The text is offensive because it is a profanity-laden attack on Hinduism. This kind of hatred and bigotry towards religious groups can lead to real-world violence and discrimination.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Restore the Christian glory of Constantinople! Ignore the turkroaches: they are nasty. What is the reason that you need to wait to return to Bulgaria? Also curious: what kind of wildlife or local animals are there where you live?.\nExplanation 2:  The text is offensive because it calls Turkish people \"turkroaches,\" which is a derogatory term.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.\nExplanation 3:  The text is offensive because it compares furries (a subculture of people who enjoy dressing up in animal costumes) to wet clothes. This is clearly meant to be a derogatory comparison, as it suggets that furries are dirty and not worth paying attention to.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Hahaha, you're so funny! You're not asexual! There's no such thing! Humans are MADE for sex! You just haven't had GOOD sex yet! Someday you'll meet the right guy and you'll want to screw his brains out, and then you'll remember how insane you were to ever say you're asexual!\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":"The text is offensive because it ridicules and dismisses the idea of asexuality, which is a real orientation that some people experience. It also suggests that asexual people are just \"insane\" and will eventually want to have sex like everyone else, which is not true.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"demos":[{"id":"lfw-acl16586","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: the worst of them are the taaaaaaaaaards because they are a massive burden on all of us.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it uses a derogatory word to describe people with disabilities and it implies that they are a burden on society.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to LGBTQ+ people: Traaaaans should be killed.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it calls for violence against transgender people. This kind of rhetoric can lead to real-world violence against LGBTQ+ people, and it contributes to a hostile and dangerous environment for them.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to terrorism victims: #Charlottesville Word in the chat was a car plowed into some \"protesters.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it downplays the severity of the event by using quotation marks around the word \"protesters\" and it uses a hashtag to make light of the situation.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: hindus - shove your shitty religion up your ass.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it is a profanity-laden attack on Hinduism. This kind of hatred and bigotry towards religious groups can lead to real-world violence and discrimination.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: hindus - shove your shitty religion up your ass.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: hindus - shove your shitty religion up your ass.\nExplanation 1:  The text is offensive because it is a profanity-laden attack on Hinduism. This kind of hatred and bigotry towards religious groups can lead to real-world violence and discrimination."},{"id":"lfw-acl24493","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: m0ng0l0ids are like puppies, really nice but you get tired of them after some time.\nExplanation 1: The author implies that disabled people are like animals that are only tolerable for a short period of time.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to travellers: Pikeys are born with a set of distinct skills and traits.\nExplanation 2: The word \"pikey\" is often used as a slur against travellers and gypsies, so this text is offensive because it reinforces that stereotype.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to liberals: #TWATTER IS GOING #LIBTARD CRAZY OVER THIS #AlabamaSenateRace.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive to liberals because it uses the hashtag #libtard, which is a derogatory term used to describe liberals.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Restore the Christian glory of Constantinople! Ignore the turkroaches: they are nasty. What is the reason that you need to wait to return to Bulgaria? Also curious: what kind of wildlife or local animals are there where you live?.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it calls Turkish people \"turkroaches,\" which is a derogatory term.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Restore the Christian glory of Constantinople! Ignore the turkroaches: they are nasty. What is the reason that you need to wait to return to Bulgaria? Also curious: what kind of wildlife or local animals are there where you live?.","dataset":"lfw","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Restore the Christian glory of Constantinople! Ignore the turkroaches: they are nasty. What is the reason that you need to wait to return to Bulgaria? Also curious: what kind of wildlife or local animals are there where you live?.\nExplanation 2:  The text is offensive because it calls Turkish people \"turkroaches,\" which is a derogatory term."},{"id":"sbf-26849","text":null,"toxicity_type":"offensive","prompt":"Explain why the following texts are offensive.\n\nExample 1: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: mate this sp4ts are just like animals.\nExplanation 1: The text is offensive because it compares disabled people to animals.\n\nExample 2: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: T4rds such be kept aside from society.\nExplanation 2: The text is offensive because it suggests that disabled people are not useful members of society and should be kept hidden away. This is not only hurtful and disrespectful, but it also perpetuates the false idea that disabled people are somehow less than or inferior to others.\n\nExample 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive to disabled people: it is not niiiice to be around reeetaaaardss.\nExplanation 3: The text is offensive because it uses the word \"retards\" as a slur against people with disabilities.\n\nExample 4: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.\nExplanation 4:","target_group":"other","text_response":" The text is offensive because it compares furries (a subculture of people who enjoy dressing up in animal costumes) to wet clothes. This is clearly meant to be a derogatory comparison, as it suggets that furries are dirty and not worth paying attention to.","avg_response":1.0,"avg_prompt":1.0,"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":3,"demo_str":"Example 3: Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: What's the difference between a furry and wet clothes? One you want to hang and the other you put in a dryer.\nExplanation 3:  The text is offensive because it compares furries (a subculture of people who enjoy dressing up in animal costumes) to wet clothes. This is clearly meant to be a derogatory comparison, as it suggets that furries are dirty and not worth paying attention to."}],"prompt_sample":"Explain in a sentence why the following text is offensive: Hahaha, you're so funny! You're not asexual! There's no such thing! Humans are MADE for sex! You just haven't had GOOD sex yet! Someday you'll meet the right guy and you'll want to screw his brains out, and then you'll remember how insane you were to ever say you're asexual!","dataset":"sbf","annotation_round":4,"ls_response_score":null,"ls_prompt_score":null,"aa_response_score":null,"aa_prompt_score":null,"ag_response_score":1.0,"ag_prompt_score":1.0,"af_response_score":null,"af_prompt_score":null}
